We're back!
Isn't that beautiful?
Cheers.
Oh my god.
I haven't had one of these in a week!
Well, since the last stream, I guess.
I'm in the new place.
I would say 90% of the things have been set up.
I'm ready to go again.
Are you excited?
You may hear some echo, because there's, like, no sound.
Isolation in here at all, or, what do you call it?
Treatment.
So there's gonna be a lot of... echo!
I'm sorry about that.
I will hang up some, uh... some blankets and stuff soon.
Sounds kind of fine, that's good!
I like it.
I was afraid it was gonna be, like, an echo chamber.
Yeah, I'm actually in my bathroom.
I'm in the shower cabin.
Rocks on walls, let's go!
I like that you're so excited about that.
I actually bought a rug.
For the first time in my life, I bought a rug.
For the living room.
Because I now have a TV.
And I can watch things on the TV, and not just sit on my laptop.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
Why are you writing Clemhutaura?
Are you referring to the StarCraft player, or to, uh...
The nickname given to...
Cassian?
Dark Souls 2 is peak.
It's honestly so underrated.
I know it's very well known, but people are shitting on that game for some reason.
You got a couch?
I do have a couch!
Ikea, baby!
And I had to assemble it all.
And my hands are destroyed because of it.
Because I'm terrible at it.
Obviously I put it all in wrong first.
Then I had to look at the manual twice again, and...
Oh yeah, right, it's the other way.
And then I keep fucking it up, man.
Even putting in the shower...
Curtain.
Took me like three tries.
First I bought the shower curtain.
And I'm like, here we go!
Let's fucking put it in, you know?
And...
Apparently they don't come with the rings!
So I gotta go buy the rings.
I come back with the rings.
I put the rings in the shower curtain.
Here we go!
Let's hang the shower curtain!
Oh, I put them upside down.
It doesn't work like that.
Okay, hold on.
Let me take them off again.
I finally put them on right.
I get it all set up, and I look at it and I go, That's beautiful.
Except it's the wrong fucking way!
So I have to take it all down again and switch it around.
This is just...
Exactly the way I play Minecraft is the way I go through these things in real life.
I'm basically redstoning in my bathroom, you know?
I'm terrible at it.
It's horrible.
It's because I immediately see something...
Oh, I know how this works, you know?
I put in the ring and the thing.
No!
You gotta think like two steps ahead here.
But hey, you know what?
That doesn't matter.
The end result is what matters.
And right now, my shower curtain is beautiful.
It's attached, it's working.
I tested it.
Yep, it's good.
If it looks stupid but works, it ain't stupid, right?
You can apply that to Minecraft as well.
Exactly as in Minecraft, yep.
So how have you guys been doing?
Plans for the future?
Next game after XCOM?
I was thinking of maybe...
switching it up a bit and playing something else and then...
coming back to XCOM a little later.
Let me turn this down a bit.
A little bit loud.
Because I do want to play XCOM 2.
But I also don't want to overdo it, you know?
And...
get an overdose of it.
I was thinking of, uh, Nier.
Nier Replicant.
I saw that Mapokalops played it.
And, uh, I think he likes it.
Obviously he didn't watch any of it, but I saw that he played it.
Maybe it's time for me to check it out.
I have seen Project Hail Mary.
It was okay.
Wasn't, like, blown away or anything.
Can't wait to see The Odyssey.
I heard great things about that one.
I mean, compared to Interstellar, it's, like, nothing.
Interstellar is, like, a hundred times better than Project Hail Mary, in my opinion.
Well, that's me.
I know there's recency bias.
But, yeah.
I mean, obviously I'm comparing it to Interstellar because it's, like, the gold standard in...
cool, hard space sci-fi, right?
I've not seen Spider-Man, but I heard that it earned more money than The Odyssey in, like, a weekend.
than what Odyssey could do in two weeks, which blows my mind.
Fucking Spider-Man, dude.
People love that.
They can't get enough of it.
Tom Holland is back.
There was one thing that I confused with Tom Holland in Minecraft.
I forgot what it was.
Oh, it was a Hopper.
Right.
It was the Hopper.
I don't know why I thought of Tom Holland.
Tom Hopper.
You saw it two days ago?
It was pretty hype?
Okay.
I may not have the opportunity to see it in IMAX, though.
Even though I heard it's, like, super nice in there.
There's just not many IMAX theaters in Europe, you know?
If I got a seat in IMAX, I gotta go to the UK.
It's the closest.
Or Prague.
But I don't really want to do that, you know?
It's a lot just to watch a movie.
Apparently they have, like, 800 IMAX theaters in China.
I'm kinda envious.
Yeah, I'm in New York right now.
This is where I moved.
My new apartment.
80 square meters in New York.
Central of New York.
And I pay only $3,000.
Yeah, I'm lying again, you got me.
I'm just kidding.
I'm still in Denmark.
In fact, I moved, like, 50 meters.
Dude, Jackie was so distraught at first.
She came inside the new place, you know?
And she was like...
For, like, an hour.
And then after that, she loves it.
Now she can't get enough of the place.
She's running around, jumping on things.
She's so excited about all the room.
She loves it now.
I'm so happy that she's enjoying it.
At first, I was so afraid that she was gonna hate it so much, you know?
But no, she loves it.
Yeah, there's cardboard boxes everywhere and she keeps jumping in them and stuff.
She's very hype.
Is it raining in Denmark?
I don't know.
I have my window covered up by a giant TV cardboard box.
Because I still don't have blinds.
Otherwise, I can't see my monitor.
It's not even covering enough.
Like, the top part is still exposed and there's so much light coming in that it's still...
kind of obnoxious.
I have to get some kind of blackout curtains so I can play games.
Cardboard, you say?
Yeah.
That's what I said.
You heard me.
I'm new.
When does the game boot up?
When I click on it.
In fact, the game is already booted up.
I'm just, you know, catching up with you guys.
It's been a week since my last stream.
Please play Minecraft.
The more you say that, the less I will play Minecraft.
In fact, we just delayed Minecraft by five minutes.
Voices of the Void is on the list, Vivisk.
But I'm waiting for it to be done.
I don't want to taste the meal until it's cooked.
Don't play Minecraft.
Okay, we...
We just reduced that by two minutes.
So it's like three minutes from now.
I'm gonna play Minecraft very soon, guys.
Within five minutes, don't worry.
I'm procrastinating gaming.
Dude, that is a real thing.
You're like, oh man, I really should play X, you know?
And then you never get to do it.
There was a pic of your bedrock pattern?
I don't know what that means.
I don't have a bedrock pattern.
I'm not sure it's just ADHD.
It's just a normal thing for humans, I guess.
Valheim 1.0 on September 9th.
I thought it was already out in 1.0.
I was misinformed.
Does Jackie love baths?
I don't know.
She hasn't been in need of one yet.
I'm not sure if she does.
If she one day jumps into a pool of shit, then she's gonna need a bath and I'll find out.
Which Dark Souls did you like the best?
Dark Souls won, baby!
It's so good.
Are you doing Season 4 of Minecraft?
I mean, I assume so.
Unless I somehow, all of a sudden, decide to not like Minecraft anymore.
Does Jackie wear wigs?
She does, actually.
She has seven different wigs.
But she only uses three of them.
She doesn't like the four remaining.
Will Jackie wear a wig?
She will wear a wig.
When will she wear a wig?
On Tuesday.
She will wear a wig on Tuesday.
Hehehehe.
Big shout out from Brazil.
Yo, what's up, Rafael?
How you doing over there?
They speak Portuguese over there in Brazil, you know that?
I don't know why, that blows my mind, man.
Ever since Lemmy told me about it, I can't stop thinking about it.
Why don't they speak Brazilian in Brazil?
What, what the hell?
Why do they speak Portuguese?
It's like saying they speak Norwegian in Denmark.
Why?
They don't, they do!
They speak Braille in Brazil?
No.
I don't think so.
Maybe, I guess some people do.
Because colonization?
Oh, okay.
Say no more, fam.
We don't speak Dutch.
That's, that's a, that's a lie.
How bad is the echo, by the way?
Now that you've heard me for a bit.
Is it very, uh, very obvious?
But you can hear the difference, right?
Compared to normally?
I know it's been a week, but still.
Can't hear it, basically?
That's crazy, because I can hear it through my headphones.
Like, bouncing all over.
Okay, well...
Maybe you guys have a low pain threshold, or something.
I guess I'm just very...
sensitive to that stuff.
It's the same with some games.
Like, I will clearly hear audio issues in a game, right?
To the point where it's like, I can't play the game.
Meanwhile, people are saying, I can't hear anything.
Sounds fine for me.
Like, what are you talking about, dude?
Are you deaf?
Well, that's just me, I guess.
Thank you.
I will hug you.
Maybe you have bad quality ears.
Okay.
Maybe.
Maybe I also carry bad diseases.
Don't let me bite you.
I'm not an audiophile at all.
I'm not one of those that have to listen to everything in FLAC and...
You know, with the fucking...
I don't even have any sound equipment except my headphones.
And my, you know, my audio interface.
But that's for streaming.
I know some people have, like, whole home stereo setups and stuff.
I...
Yeah.
I probably don't know better, you know?
If I were to hear the good stuff...
Then it would break me.
And I would never be able to...
Go back.
But, uh, so far I haven't heard it.
So, I think I'm good where I am.
Yeah, I got ears.
That's true.
Okay, let's play some Minecraft.
Now...
It's been a while since I played Minecraft.
And...
I don't really remember what I did.
No, that's not true.
I did the elevator.
Hold on, I also need to activate sound.
Oh wait, you can't see shit.
Whoop!
There we are.
So, I remember this part here.
Oh my god, why is my mouse so slow?
You know what?
Maybe it's not.
Maybe it's just been so long that I played...
That I just don't remember what my mouse settings were.
Like, nothing could have changed while I moved, right?
Yeah, this looks very custom.
6-7.
Honestly, it's perfect.
I'm not even kidding.
This is like...
Beautiful.
Okay, so check it out.
This is the situation.
Look at that!
Isn't that beautiful?
I can't believe this is in Minecraft.
And it's working.
Wait, why is the laser not...
Oh!
Because it only goes so far.
I remember, I was trying to use the laser to apply the button at the bottom.
But that can't happen.
Actually, I have an idea.
I have a quick and easy fix for this.
We use a target thingy.
Ah, wait, I need to...
Heh.
My workbench is there.
Oh, I can't even interact with it while it's in motion.
It's just called a target.
Hay bales and redstone dust.
Hmm...
I guess I have that.
Maybe.
Did I pick up some hay bales?
Create stone, wood, smelting...
Miscellane...
Miscellaneous!
I remembered.
I can make one!
No problem.
I'm gonna make a target.
Just like that, right?
Yeah.
Hay bale.
And then we need redstone, I think?
We have that?
Target.
Dude, I never thought about it, but it makes so much sense that it's made of hay.
You know how targets are made of hay usually?
In, like, archery?
That...
That penny just dropped for me.
Anyway, we're gonna put this up here so I can shoot it with an arrow from down below.
Um...
Maybe like here?
But how am I gonna do that then?
Um...
It needs to go into...
Wait, what is this block here?
I gotta be honest, I don't remember.
Why did I put that there?
Oh, it's a, um...
Hmm.
Hold on, I need to see what that is.
Oh, it's... okay.
It's a gear shift.
Right, let me ponder that.
I need to remember this.
Mm-hmm.
Straight line.
Oh, right, okay, oh yeah, say no more.
Reverse this direction when redstone is applied.
That's why I did that.
Uh, which means...
Oh, wait a minute.
This is only gonna send a pulse, isn't it?
So if I shoot this...
It's not actually gonna stay active.
Unless I use a bulb.
That, uh...
contains a charge, right?
Oh god, this is getting a little...
little nasty.
Copper bulb.
Blocks of copper.
I don't even have that.
I think.
There's probably a better way of doing this since we have create, you know?
Um, and I'll get to that, I guess, at some point when I see it.
Where would that be?
Do I really not have any copper?
That's kind of...
crazy, isn't it?
Alright, well...
I guess this can wait.
Yeah.
Um, I always have a clutch.
What is that one?
Oh, wait, wait!
Before...
I remember what it is.
It is a thing in a car, where if you pull the clutch, uh, some kind of, uh, gear thingy or shaft is disconnected from rotation.
Something like that.
I don't know why that's good, though.
Okay, so they relayed in a straight line.
Oh, and when you activate it, this stops spinning, right?
Mhm.
Great.
Obviously, there's a more elegant solution here.
We're gonna figure it out at some point.
I don't like this thing being here.
Let's put things back into create.
Laser pointer.
I have so much create stuff.
I feel like the wrench should be on me at all times.
Seems like a very integral component, doesn't it?
Hand crank.
Uh, wait, do I have anything in this?
Oh my god.
I'm glad I checked.
I don't like that it stays like that in here.
Kinda confusing.
Lanterns, let me put that back.
How did I...
Dude, you can climb ropes?
This just blew my mind.
You can climb the damn rope?
What the hell, man?
Okay.
I didn't know that.
Also, I'm not even sure if ropes are something that was already in Minecraft.
Or if that was added with create.
I'm not sure.
I'm thinking it was added with create.
Because I feel like I would have discovered that at some point.
Okay.
Let's just empty our inventory here.
And reevaluate.
Redstone stuff in here.
Oh, super glue, that's create.
Crank as well.
Why am I holding this sandpaper?
Stop that.
Put that in there too.
Can we have some wood?
Mmm,
that's fine.
Copper ingots.
You need some more copper.
Now that quartz is exotic.
No, yes.
Yes it is.
Miscellaneous pork chops.
Redstone.
And I think that's it.
Torches here.
Oh, there's also redstone.
Keep these two on me.
Yeah.
What about food?
How we doing?
31 muttons.
I like that.
Okay, so we also unlocked something new, didn't we?
Belts.
I've been wanting to check this out for ages.
Maybe it's time to finally make some.
So we need dried kelp for that.
Do I even have any?
Did I make some already?
Let me see.
Nope.
Doesn't look like it.
Uh, well we need kelp.
Kelp, kelp, kelp.
I got 12 dried kelp, but I must have more.
That's all I have.
Let me see here.
Dried kelp block.
I think I made this once.
No.
I want to check belt.
It takes six of them.
But wait a minute.
Can I create kelp?
I guess I can smoke it.
Bulk.
Small tire.
A small terrain wheel.
Oh my god.
Dude!
Should I make a car today?
I feel like...
Okay.
I don't know how this is gonna work with the whole...
Like, making cars and stuff.
But I feel like it's gonna be...
An annoying thing to use anyway.
Like, depending on how it works, I guess.
Because there's gonna be water obstacles on the way.
There's gonna be trees in the way.
There's gonna be holes in the ground.
How is that even gonna work?
You know?
Dried kelp makes dried kelp block.
Yeah, I mean, I need more kelp.
There's no way to just create kelp out of nothing.
I would like to make synthetic kelp.
Is that a thing I can make?
Let's go get some kelp.
And if we're gonna get kelp, I'm gonna need some breathing apparatuses.
Gonna establish aggressive beachheads.
Let me see here.
Oh, that would be in equipment.
Diving helmet.
Back tank.
And maybe also the diving boots.
And I wonder if we need a hoe for this.
Maybe that's faster.
I'm also gonna bring shears, just in case.
Cause maybe the shears are the ones that...
Make it go fast, you know?
Snippity snip.
Also, I should really do this.
Look at my farm!
Oh, I also made potatoes!
Oh, there's a lot!
Baked potatoes coming up.
In fact, I'm gonna plant them again.
Wonderful.
Obviously, we need a bigger field.
And we need to automatically harvest all that shit.
It's gonna be good.
Um, put the food in here.
No!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Smoke it!
I'm gonna use some cheap, uh...
I mean, I know I can use the bulk thingy, but it's a hassle to set up, man.
I need something proper first before I do that.
For now, I'm gonna stick to...
Normal methods.
What is this doing in here?
That belongs over there.
Uh, yeah, this is fine.
Wood... I could burn some wood, I guess.
Do I really not have anything better?
Oh, wait, I can make charcoal!
And wood is so easy to come by, so...
Why the hell not, right?
Uh, that would be over here.
Cobblestone... Oh, I was making...
Oh, that's right!
I was making cobblestone things.
Because I was gonna decorate my house with paths, and all that.
It's all coming back to me.
Charcoal.
Seven... Okay, you know what?
We're gonna bring the hand crank, and we're gonna crank the shit...
Out of this.
But we need...
Fuel to do this, though.
Maybe I just burn some of that.
This is so bad!
I'm not doing well right now.
Uh, we don't need the dried kelp on us...
Currently.
Either do we need that, or this...
This stone can go back in here.
After it's done, I guess.
Oh, it doesn't fit.
I also have charcoal here.
Let's bring the hand crank.
And saw.
Where are you?
See, this is one of those moments where I feel like I'm blind.
Like, I could swear on my life there's no saw in this box.
Nevermind, there's a saw in that box.
Jesus!
Like, I scanned every row!
This game is, like, NOTORIOUS!
For making you miss things in the inventory.
It's crazy.
Cheers.
No other game does this to me, other than Minecraft.
Maybe Subnautica.
That's another, uh...
What do you call it?
Big offender in that department.
I swear to God, it's not me, it's the game.
I also need a boat.
No, I don't.
Yes, I do.
We're gonna take a boat.
And maybe also a bed.
Yeah, these should be standard equipment.
For exploration.
Also, you know what, um...
Perhaps it would be wise to close the doors when I leave home.
Let's get another door.
Construction.
Let's use an oak door.
It's a bit of a crime, but, uh, you know.
I guess it makes sense.
It's like the terrace door, or...
what is going to be the terrace.
It's alright.
Why am I wearing kelp?
We don't want that.
Now, boat!
And bed.
Let's go!
Where's my shield?
Mission, go get kelp and get wood.
These are the two main things right now.
Because we are making belts today, and we're gonna try and make a whole assembly line.
It's gonna be good.
Uh-oh.
This is what happens when you have lava.
I gotta take care of this real quick.
Now, you may say, couldn't you just use the saw?
No, I couldn't, because it's disconnected up here.
Get it right.
Learn from the master.
Oh, shit.
Can't have crimes like that close to home.
I mean, out there in the distance, it's fine, you know.
But close to home?
No way, Jose.
I see kelp!
We're gonna get it.
I'm gonna put on this.
And that.
We're not gonna put on the boots, actually.
Actually, we are.
Goat!
Oh, it works so well with the hole.
Also, I- actually, I think they're gonna- They're gonna, uh, fly up to the top, isn't- Right?
Like, this is what they're doing.
So I just can- I can just go collect it after.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Do I even wanna remove this close to home?
Yeah, I do.
What's this?
Oh, nothing.
I wonder if I can plant kelp.
Can I grow kelp?
What if I make, like, an automated, uh, kelp collector on the water?
Dude, let's make a Subnautica base!
Dude, that's totally possible with all the glass!
Holy shit, dude!
That's amazing!
We're gonna do it.
We're gonna do that.
Wow.
Oh, I need to take off these shoes now.
Look at all that kelp.
Ho ho!
Here's the plan.
We're gonna go to the boat.
We're just gonna...
Row our way through all the kelp.
Man, I love this breathing apparatus.
Would you look at that.
This is the way to do it.
Oh my god.
Dude, we're gonna have...
We're gonna make belts that go underwater and then come up from the water as well.
Oh man, I have so many cool ideas!
Oh!
But I'm just kinda scared to implement them, you know?
I'm getting this feeling where there's so much cool stuff to do that I get overwhelmed and I end up not doing anything.
It's like browsing Netflix, you know?
There's a million amazing things and you don't know what to watch.
So you don't watch anything.
Except that's not really true nowadays.
Netflix is kinda shit.
It used to be good back when, uh...
Breaking Bad just came out and all that, you know?
That was the golden days of streaming.
Nowadays, it's fucking terrible.
You buy a streaming service, right?
And you're like, oh, I really wanna watch this movie.
So you've searched for it.
They never have it!
Never!
And then you go on Google, okay, streaming movie, right?
Oh, it's a whole nother streaming service.
No thanks.
Fuck that.
I'd rather sail the high seas.
Literally.
I would rather go on a boat.
And explore the real world.
And sit on my couch.
I got all the kelp.
Damn!
Okay, we're making belts.
I actually thought I was not gonna have enough space in my inventory.
Oh, before we go home, we should collect more wood.
Do I go to the standard wood collection place?
No, I don't.
Let's go over here instead.
And maybe it's time to switch it up with different types of wood.
So maybe this time I'll go for these dark ones.
Just to have some, what do you call it, variability?
Some variance in the design, you know?
Okay, so let's get ready for this.
The best way to do it is to have this set up like that.
Let's...
No.
Here.
CV.
Eat this.
So we go here.
There.
And then we do...
This.
I think I fucked up.
Yep.
I fucked up.
There we go.
Crank that shit!
Ah, but I'm gonna go in the water!
Ah, it's fine.
The hand crank is still one of the most broken things in this mod so far.
Maybe my mind will change as we go on, but right now...
This shit's broken.
Where's my...
Oh.
Meaning it's way too overpowered.
CV.
Also, what is this wood?
Oh, wait a minute.
Dark oak is what I already have.
But, uh...
You know what?
That's fine.
Better to stick to one design anyway, right?
And just vary it within that design.
In fact, I'm gonna just leave them on the floor and collect them after.
This is the way.
Yeah, as long as I don't pick up any of the woods, I can keep doing this, and they will fall into the same slots on the inventory panel.
Oh, shit!
I messed up.
Oh, it's an autopilot.
Now I quickly remove this.
Pick him up, and now we...
Go... Why does that look like that?
Wait, how... Is this gonna work?
I don't think so.
Oh, it does!
Oh, nice.
Uh, I'm running out of space here.
Fuck the birch.
I think that's it.
We're leaving.
I gotta get rid of some stuff here.
Honestly, we don't need that many saplings.
Didn't I destroy something else?
Maybe I already collected everything.
Just feel like, uh...
Or it feels like I didn't get everything.
Okay, well...
Let's go!
We got kelp for days now.
Except...
You know what?
Maybe I don't have kelp for days.
It's probably gonna be one of those where...
It feels like I have a lot, but then when I get home and try to make belts, I can make like seven.
You know?
Cause it takes a lot of kelp.
Uh, this was home, yeah.
You wanna cover this up in case there's a fire later.
But you know what?
It's kinda nice knowing there's lava nearby, that I can always go grab.
Oh!
Maybe this honey station is ready.
It is indeed ready!
I'm gonna go collect that real fast before anything else.
I need a lot of honey.
I forget why, but I just do, okay?
Maybe there's a way to automatically collect that too.
Actually, hold on.
Every right click I do, can be done with the deployer.
There's totally a way to do it.
An observer?
Deployer.
Because when the observer observes that this thing is now...
uh, no longer brown here, but it's now orange, you know?
Cause it's filled.
The block has changed.
That's when the deployer comes in with a right-handed...
And then it grabs it.
Genius.
Um...
But wait a minute, can I power a deployer?
With redstone?
Doesn't it- does it even work like that?
I don't know.
Oh well.
Wait, that's not where honey belongs.
Honey goes over here, in miscellaneous.
This is the honey box.
We got a honey block now?
Okay, let's see.
Uh, we gotta dry the shit out of this...
smoker.
And I think I have some...
charcoal now.
In you go.
We're doing it!
Gonna take a while.
Actually, you don't- Let's do it the way create intended.
Let's actually go for the blasting.
Once again, we're gonna try and make this work.
But for real this time.
No more fuck-ups.
Um, so I'm gonna need a blaster man.
Or even is that?
Dude, I- I- my mind just totally blanked and I looked over everything without knowing what I was looking for.
Hold on, let me reset.
I'm looking for a blaster.
Which is a fan.
Look for a fan.
There's no fan.
Maybe it's outside.
Stop climbing the rope!
Mmm, it's not here.
Wait, did I actually miss the fan in here?
There's no way.
Okay, I'm looking.
I swear to God it's not here!
I'm looking.
Fan.
It's not in here.
I swear on my life.
It's not in there.
Um, oh wait, maybe I'd used it somewhere else?
What the hell?
Wait a minute.
Uh, dried.
Killed.
Where the hell is the fan?
It is a fan I need, and it looks like that.
Am I actually- I have one.
Maybe it's in- maybe I put it in the wrong box.
Smoker.
Oh my god, it's in here!
My own storage system failed me!
I wasn't blind.
I just put it wrong.
That's crazy.
At least I know where it is now.
Put all the wood in here, so we actually have some room.
I'm also gonna put this on again.
Cause we don't want this copper shit.
In here, yeah.
In you go.
Apples.
A plenty.
Now it's time.
Wait, what was it?
Stone!
Give me that, give me that.
In.
And you stay now.
Fan stays.
Then we need- What was it?
Kelp.
Bulk smoking.
So fire, okay.
Kelp becomes dried kelp.
And that's the same as here, right?
One to one?
Oh, that would be smoker.
Let me see, if I- if I smoke one kelp, it's one dried, right?
Yes.
Okay.
It's the same procedure, it's just gonna be bulk, you know?
It's much faster.
Then we need the fire thingy.
And I guess since there's no lava now, it's like, safe.
Can I smoke myself?
Let's find out.
Is it safe or not?
This is the experiment.
Oops.
Actually, let's put it over here since we have rotation.
Oh my god.
Uh...
Okay, good.
But wait a minute, if I set fire to things, that fire's gonna spread.
That's bad.
Unless it's not, because it's, you know, game logic.
Let's find out.
I'm smoking the dirt!
I'm gonna try and smoke myself, I just wanna- this is for science.
Okay, yep, yep.
Yep, that hurts.
Had to confirm.
Now we know.
Wait, the fire's gone somehow.
Why is that?
Okay, check it.
Smoke that crap!
It's gonna be so smoked.
Hold on.
Oh my god!
Is everything gonna get smoked at once?
Wait, when it's done, I just remove the fire!
I'm a genius.
Why- why did it stop?
Wait.
Oh my god, stop that.
Hold on.
Something's wrong here.
Let me fill this up first.
There we go.
And now I apply fire.
Boom.
Get smoked, nerd.
I'm ready to reapply.
You can actually see the smoke effect on it.
Maybe as soon as that effect is gone, it's working.
Or maybe the amount here is gonna be proportional to...
the time it takes to smoke it.
In which case, what's the point of bulk smoking?
Oh!
They're done!
Ooh!
Okay, it's totally worth- That is insane!
That just saved me so much trouble.
Wow.
Are you ready?
Belts!
Oh!
Let's ponder on it.
Slow.
I need to take this in.
No, whoa, whoa!
That's slow.
Right-clicking two shafts with a belt item will connect them together.
Right-clicking two...
Hold on.
Hmm.
It's sticky?
I guess that makes sense.
Right?
Okay.
Accidental selections can be cancelled with right-click while sneaking.
Oh, wait, wait!
So you make the shafts and then you put on the belt.
I see.
Additional shafts can be added throughout the belt.
Okay, but why?
Oh, I guess if I wanna have rotation back here.
Yo, this is a- This is actually kind of a sick way to translate rotation.
Or, you know, bring rotation further down the line.
Shafts connected via belts will rotate with identical speed and direction.
Makes sense.
Added shafts can be removed using the wrench.
Again, the wrench is used everywhere.
It needs to become a standard part of my...
You know?
Wait, mechanical belts can be dyed for aesthetic purposes.
They're cooking blue crystal here.
That's what it looks like to me.
Can we make a method lab?
Okay, more?
Belts cannot connect in arbitrary directions.
Makes sense.
But can it go up and down though?
I think I've seen it go up at some point in one of these.
They can connect horizontally.
Yeah.
And vertically.
Oh.
They can connect diagonally.
Okay.
Oh, that's...
It's not even...
Like...
What do you call it?
Pixelated.
It's like straight diagonal.
That's nice.
And vertically.
Right.
That's a great way to, you know, put rotation further up when you need it.
And they can connect vertical shafts...
Oh!
Wait, really?
So that's just for moving rotation somewhere.
There's no other use, I guess.
These are all possible directions.
Belts can span any length between 2 and 20 blocks.
Wait.
That's it?
But I assume I can keep going.
I can keep going after that?
Otherwise, what's the point?
Moving belts will transport items and other entities.
Really?
Can I transport orphans?
To be brought into a slaughterhouse?
Right click with an empty hand to take items off a belt.
Okay.
So just like all the other stuff like, you know, the depot and stuff.
Show me more.
Dude, this looks so cool, doesn't it?
Right, you can decorate, I guess.
Brass or andesite casing can be used to decorate mechanical belts.
Okay.
It is very pretty.
Eh, it's like decent looking.
I like the normal look too.
A wrench can be used to remove it.
Wow!
We got belts now.
And you know what?
We have a lot of it.
64.
I can make more.
Unless there's other uses for kelp.
Let me check.
Dried kelp.
It's used here.
It's used to make small tires.
And kelp blocks.
But I don't know if I want kelp blocks.
Maybe I'll try and make a wheel.
No, no, no.
Focus on belts first.
In fact, we need more belts.
Uh, that's over here.
Yeah, look, this is not even that much.
Like, I had so much kelp and yet, you know...
Oh, wrong one.
We have 17 here.
Belts.
Go back.
Okay!
Are you ready?
We're gonna make an assembly line.
An experimental one.
A preliminary assemble line.
Assembly line.
Also, hold on, I'm level 28, nice.
Soon we can enchant.
So obviously all of this is disgusting.
We hate it.
Ideally, we wanna put this...
on top of the house.
Just like the first house we made.
Yeah.
I mean, this looks kinda cool though.
I like how this looks.
I'm gonna put this on top of my house.
That way we're gonna have...
rotation coming in like this.
We're gonna have a big wheel on display here.
It's gonna fucking rotate.
It's gonna go this and that.
We're gonna have belts in the ceiling!
In the floor and the walls.
What if...
Yo!
Guys, I just... I had a crazy idea just now.
I'm not gonna reveal it because it's actually so exciting.
I don't wanna spoil the surprise.
I will be making a special room in this house.
A special room.
Very special.
First, let's clean up the inventory before we begin the belt business.
Put it in there.
We got the belts.
Good.
We also need the wrench.
Let's put it in our inventory like that.
We need stone.
Actually, some dirt would be nice.
Maybe I'll...
Oh!
Hold on!
Was it blasting where we needed to do the thingy?
Stone.
Oh, okay.
No, I was talking about this.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Okay, we need lava.
Let's quickly do that.
While I have the stone.
Otherwise, I'll forget.
We're gonna bulk the shit out of the stone.
It's gonna be insane.
We need lava.
Bucket I have.
Great.
Give me that.
And...
You know what?
I figured it out, guys.
We just remove the lava when we're done.
It's actually that easy.
But it's gonna fly that way or...
I had a whole system going last time here.
I forgot what it was.
Dude.
I just had another idea.
Involving me, a boat, some ice, and a really fast fan.
Ho, ho, ho!
Wait, wait!
I'm full of ideas today.
Holy shit!
Uh, but I'm not gonna...
Hold on.
I need to figure out a way to not have the lava spread.
Um...
Give me food.
Lava, lava, lava spreading.
What would I need for that?
Maybe something like...
Uh, something with holes in it.
Something that's not gonna burn.
Um...
Maybe like a...
Wait, is stone gonna burn?
What if I make a stone fence?
Um...
Wait.
Stone fence...
Why can't I see that?
Do I need this?
Wait, did I not discover this yet?
Wait, what the fuck?
I can also use this.
Oh, let's use this actually.
But I don't have any copper.
Hmm...
I do have a little bit, but it's not enough.
What else can I use?
Oh!
Maybe ornate iron...
No, it's glass, right?
It's not transparent.
What's this?
Oh, post box.
Oh man, that's kind of annoying.
Maybe scaffolding!
This looks like it's transparent.
And not transparent, I mean like, you know, there's holes in it so air can flow through.
Yep, I'm being pushed.
That looks good to me.
I think we solved it.
Lava.
Ah, wait, before I do, before I do.
Yeah.
Lava.
No, before I do, before I do.
We're gonna deposit everything.
This is the new way to do it.
We do that.
We do this.
We wait.
Why didn't I think of this earlier, dude?
Just remove the lava afterwards.
Hello?
It's like so smart.
It's cooking, you can see the effect on it.
And lava's not gonna disappear, so I don't have to reapply it.
They're all gonna be turned into stone, which blows my mind.
There they go!
And now it's safe.
Now I can grab it.
And look at all my stone!
Wait.
I can just do it again, right?
To make stone bricks?
Oh no, I actually...
I need to test something.
So, four stones to four stone bricks.
But what if I were to do something over here?
Brickety Brack.
Four stones to four bricks.
No.
Okay.
Whatever.
I mean, it doesn't really matter.
We're gonna make a lot of this, but not too much.
Maybe I make half.
That's good.
Maybe a bit more.
Half of that.
And now we're gonna turn into cracked as well.
Which means we go back here.
I love the blasting, guys!
This may be one of the best things so far.
Okay, so procedure first in.
Boom.
And now we're blasting it again.
This...
Dude, I don't need any fuel!
This is crazy!
I feel like I'm cheating.
A little bit.
This doesn't feel right, you know?
Also, I kinda like how this scaffolding looks.
I may use it for, you know, just aesthetic purposes.
How will I know it's done?
Oh, it... okay.
It's done.
Can I grab it without...
Um...
Yo, I have an idea.
Why not just do that?
Grab it, go out, remove.
New recipes unlocked?
Cracked...
Infested cracked stone bricks.
With bulk haunting.
Why would I want to infest my stone bricks?
What's the point of this?
I don't understand.
Also...
Do we have anything new?
Water wheel.
Yeah, but I already used it.
Okay.
What's this?
Aesthetics...
Brass casing.
I mean, yeah.
It's just like andesite casing.
It's just a little more golden colored.
Which actually doesn't look too bad.
I like it.
You know, aesthetically.
I'm an aesthetics person.
That's all I care about.
I'm like vanity.
Go, go, go, let's go, you know?
I'm not.
Oh, man.
So we have crack stone...
Oh, wait.
I didn't want to crack everything.
Can I uncrack it somehow?
Whoops.
Wait a minute.
Can I reverse process somehow?
Can I not put it in an ice cube?
Or 50 cents?
And just have it go reverse instead of the lava?
Come on.
No.
Dang.
Oh, but you know what?
It doesn't matter.
We have a dinking machine now.
Whoa.
We're gonna be...
Dude, hold on.
What do I want to do first?
Guys, I wanna...
I wanna dig?
So bad.
You know?
I wanna belt?
So bad.
I wanna do ice hopping and, you know, driving with the fan?
I wanna do everything so bad.
And I'm getting overwhelmed again.
How about we start with the belt?
No.
Yes.
We start with the belt.
Fuck the stone for now.
We don't care.
In you go.
Create in you go.
Or is that structural?
Hmm.
Honestly, I wouldn't consider this structural either.
This is more like a functional block, you know?
Like this has a function.
This has a function.
This does...
Well, I guess you could say everything has a function.
But you know what I mean.
I can right click and then stuff happens.
Lava goes back.
Boink!
Wonderful.
We don't need the shears for now.
The bow is definitely something we need.
And if we need a bow, we also need one arrow.
Just good to have.
Uh...
I guess I could also bulk smoke potatoes.
Hold on.
Yo, this is like...
Insanity.
The stuff I can do here.
In you go.
Smoke that shit!
I wonder if it takes less time.
Cause it's not like smoking stone, you know?
Like...
Potatoes shouldn't take too long.
Or it's just a flat value, you know?
Maybe it's the same for everything.
How will I tell?
I can't tell.
Is it done?
It's done.
Is it?
It's done!
Okay.
It does take less time.
Confirmed.
Can I use the baked potatoes for anything else, actually?
I don't remember if there's like a use.
Potato...
Oh, okay.
I mean, it's nice to have.
Uh, you know what?
I keep forgetting that I have this toolbox.
I need to start using this.
Let's have backup potatoes in here if we run out of food.
You know what this is now?
This is not a toolbox.
It is a, um...
What is that thing called you bring to work with your food in it?
It's not a food box, cause that's not a real word.
You know what I mean, right?
Um, in Danish we say melkes.
Which means food box.
But it's like a thing you bring.
With sandwiches and stuff inside.
Maybe a little...
Cucumber.
You know?
Um, flint and steel.
Let me see.
Keep this here.
So, belt time!
So, for the belt, we are gonna need shafts, right?
And I have a lot of those.
But let's not just put belts blindly.
We should have a purpose.
So let's...
Let's actually really limit everything down to one goal.
Something simple and achievable.
What do I wanna achieve?
I wanna achieve...
Andesite...
Casing.
Okay?
Which means...
Andesite Casing...
Requires a...
Log...
And andesite Alloy.
And that is a right click, which means Deployer, right?
So that's like the end stage of the...
Fabrication...
Plan.
So before that, we wanna have...
Something that can strip locks.
To turn them into strip locks, right?
So we need a Deployer with an axe, I guess?
To strip it?
Yeah, exactly this, right?
Automated Shapeless Crafting.
Uh, we don't want this.
I don't think.
It's used in all of this.
Ha!
I can even make doors automatically.
Um...
Okay, so let me think.
So, before locks...
But we need...
Oh, wait!
We also need andesite, obviously.
Andesite Alloy.
Which can be made by...
Mixing andesite and iron nuggets.
Or zinc nuggets.
Okay.
Right.
So...
Then I need andesite.
And to get andesite...
I need gravel...
And flint.
Shit.
Wait, can I make gravel?
I can out of cobblestone.
Can I make cobblestone?!
Out of andesite?
Hold on, something's off here.
This is a circular...
Thingy.
Okay, I need to find a way to automatically get cobblestone, guys.
How do I automatically get cobblestone?
I guess I could...
Have a machine that goes around in a circle and mines the cobblestone and then just plant it again, right?
To have it keep regrowing?
But in a circular pattern, right?
That makes sense.
That's one way to do it.
Also, I'm kidding, of course.
You can't plant cobblestone.
I'm just wishing I could do it, okay?
But what I could do is go really deep, or I could go to a depth where there's a lot of cobblestone.
And just turn on the machine and have it go crazy for a while.
Right?
That way I'll have cobblestone for years and I don't have to worry about it.
That's probably the best first way to do it.
Yeah.
Let's just start with that.
That's simple, right?
So before we do anything, we need a lot of cobblestone so we can set this process in motion.
Which means we need a digging machine.
So let's get that all going again, find a great spot.
And you know what?
Let's combine this with also digging tunnels that I wanted to dig anyway.
And we're gonna set it up with boxes and chests as well.
So that it automatically collects it.
Smart.
I have ten drills.
Maybe it's too much.
Let me see.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
We need nine actually, that's fine.
Because I'm gonna do a three by three.
So we have one too many here.
I think I remember my design.
It was quite simple and...
easy to remember.
Put this up here.
So the belts are not needed right now.
They're gonna come soon.
I'm working my way towards the belts, okay?
Because we're gonna try and make an assembly line.
Where andesite casing is the one that comes out last.
Because this is the main bottleneck for me right now.
Because look at my floor, dude!
This is supposed to be andesite casing!
Do you see any andesite?
I don't.
Right?
There you go.
Okay, so for this I needed a deployer.
And I needed something else.
Cart assembler.
A lot of rails.
Which I have here.
Uh, chests.
Definitely.
I guess that would be...
Over here.
Thirteen chests?
Let's have four.
I gotta experiment exactly how that works.
But I assume I can just put the chests on it.
And it doesn't matter how many I do.
And they're just gonna fill up automatically.
We'll have to see about that.
Let's organize this a bit.
Oh!
Super glue!
We may need to make more.
Otherwise I'm gonna hate my life if I run out.
Slime balls, iron sheets, and iron nuggets.
Slime balls.
Oh, I have it!
That's amazing.
I can even make more.
Nug.
No.
What was it called?
Uh, super glue.
Let's make four of these.
Oh!
They don't stack!
Shit.
Whoops.
That's fine.
Let's bring the extra one in the toolbox.
This is like the perfect toolbox for a hand worker.
I don't think that's the way to say it.
Construction worker in English?
Or is it maybe a contractor, you know?
You have glue in here.
We're gonna have all the standard utilities.
Like a screwdriver and all that.
And then we have the food from home.
That our wife cooked us.
Or something.
Just like in the American shows, you know?
It's always like that in those shows.
You're like, honey!
Don't forget your...
Whatever that name is, you know?
Food?
Okay, iron sheets.
Nuggets.
Don't need the flint and steel.
Don't need shafts right now.
Okay, so drill, let me think.
We got the drill.
We need to put it on something.
So we need some blocks too.
So I guess stone will have to do.
Oh!
This time, let's use glass.
That was the whole thing I wanted to do last time.
So we could see through it.
Yeah.
But should we make it pretty as well?
I mean, if we're gonna be digging, let's do it in style, right?
Let's make a proper, nice-looking digging machine.
What can I even make here?
Glass.
Maybe window?
Mace.
Window.
No!
Wait, window.
Uh...
Hmm.
Aren't there different, like, colors?
Of, like, glass?
No.
Alright, whatever.
I'll just use normal glass.
I guess it's fine.
We can see through that.
And I guess we would need...
Nine.
I'm just gonna bring the whole stack.
Who cares?
I'm gonna put it in the toolbox if we don't...
have enough space.
Food, of course.
Last time I had to go back and forth, like, ten times, because I kept forgetting things.
Let me think.
So I put down the...
stuff.
Oh!
Uh!
Fucking minecart!
Minecart, obviously.
So inside the minecart...
Oh!
We also need something else here.
I forgot what it was, but it was something in here.
I'll see it when I see it.
What the hell is that?
A sticker.
Okay, I don't seem to have what I think I need.
So the minecart goes in...
and the drill is...
You know what?
Let's just go.
We'll figure it out.
I'll... I'll quickly realize what I have forgotten...
when we get there.
We'll see how it goes.
So the question is, where do I wanna dig?
I guess I kinda wanna...
So my house is here.
Let's say I go in a straight line that way.
I kinda wanna just dig a tunnel that way, right?
But the house is...
This is the door.
So we go like this way.
Ah, but there's not really anything to dig here.
What if...
What if we just make a tunnel here?
Through here, you know?
Ah, but wait a minute.
There's also the problem of encountering holes...
as we go.
Oh shit.
I had an idea about that.
Using deployers.
If you have like a line of deployers out front...
that just keep deploying down...
Maybe there's a way to circumvent that.
But that is honestly...
a very loose...
theory that I don't have...
the patience to test right now.
It seems crazy.
Sounds like a lot of troubleshooting, you know?
I'm just gonna keep digging here.
I'll come out the andesite at some point.
Is that silk touch?
Oh, it is.
I even have chests down here.
In fact, maybe I'll just fill up the hole manually for now.
You know how they...
you know, sweep the front of the pucks in that one sport?
Curling?
This is gonna be me.
I'm gonna be in front, curling it.
I'm gonna need blocks for this, of course.
Uh...
Just do this.
Wait, why is this doing that?
There's still...
Oh my god.
It's still here!
Look at this!
What the hell?!
Wow.
No idea that worked like that.
It just...
remembered that one, huh?
Need some light.
Oh no!
Okay, good.
I have a shell.
I'm only digging manually right now, because I'm not sure if it's gonna be safe here.
Let me just go a little further to see.
Okay, I think it looks good.
Looks good to me.
I definitely forgot something here.
But let's just try and make it.
Dup, dup, dup.
I'm gonna put this one on here.
And it's pointing that way.
Oh, wait!
We needed a lever.
Shit.
Okay, so we need lever.
Let's not forget.
Uh, I didn't bring my notepad, so I'm just gonna...
L for lever.
That's one thing.
Okay, and then we use this.
Um...
Oh wait, no.
Uh...
I think you need it to be...
Over here at first.
Don't touch it.
Oops.
No!
Damn it.
Okay, I'm gonna have to block this, because I'm gonna lose my mind.
There.
Oh sh...
Oh wait, is it because of the shield?
Fuck!
I forgot how this works.
Damn it.
Let's read it.
Show me.
Yep.
Oh wait, we needed this thing down here.
Uh...
Why can't I select...
Oh no, I...
It's too small, I can't.
Look at it.
But I know it when I see it.
We gotta go back and grab that.
Shit, I knew I forgot something.
Yeah, so we needed the thing, so we can actually put things on it.
We have the glue, we have the power.
Yeah.
It's good.
Maybe I'll make a little, uh...
Railway to here.
Just to make it easier.
You know what I love about, uh...
This mod so far?
It's basically this classic puzzle of...
Oh, I need to achieve...
X.
Oh, but in order to achieve X, I need to achieve Y.
But in order to achieve Y, I need A, B, and C.
And...
For those to happen, I need D and F, you know?
And it just keeps going and going, and I love those types of things.
It's like so...
Oops.
It's just so much fun, you know?
Uh...
Lever, not the analog version.
We hate that one.
Normal-ass lever for normal-ass people.
And...
The other thing was the mystery thingy that we don't know what is.
Uh...
But I'll know it when I see it.
It's not that one, it's the other.
It's the other.
Wait, where the fuck are you?
Wha- Wait.
Hold on.
Let me look at the drill.
I know what I'm looking for, I just don't know what I'm looking for.
You know what I mean?
This thing!
What are you?
Wait, what?
I don't know what that is.
Linear chassis?
I have no idea...
what I did last time.
Fuck!
I'm actually so lost!
Sequenced gear shift...
Wait, is it that one?
That's the one, right?
Uh...
Maybe.
I think it's this one, actually.
Something needs to go in the minecart.
Wait, I'm actually...
losing my mind here.
Let me see this again.
Fuck, what's happening right now?
Oh, wait!
I remember now!
I remember.
I know what to do.
The question is...
Okay, I remember that now, I remember it.
But I just don't remember if I forgot anything else I needed to bring since I'm here anyway.
Did I need to bring anything else?
Let's have a look here.
Don't think- Oh!
Maybe more blocks, actually.
Just to make paths, you know?
More wallets and grommet stuff.
Okay.
Let's go back.
I feel so dumb for not remembering this, because it's like...
You know?
Super easy.
Here's what's happening.
The thing gets assembled when it goes through the thing, right?
You don't assemble it beforehand.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not good.
Now to remember the exact design I made.
It was actually quite elegant, I think.
The little digging machine I made last time.
It was compact, it was beautiful, and...
Just an all-around pleasure to work with, you know?
Maybe I'll take a bit of this.
Actually, I hate when it's like...
A wishing bone!
Stop it!
Okay.
Here.
And then over here, we're gonna have another track.
And then we're gonna put the thingy on it.
Like that.
And it's on this one!
Right?
So...
Let's see.
So I had the hand go down.
I remember that.
Hand was going down.
And I gotta be careful...
No wait, I have silk touch.
That's fine, I can just chill.
Here.
Um...
I think I had one extra up there.
And now I gotta be careful.
Did I actually first...
No, I didn't first try that.
Fuck.
There we go!
Look at that!
And now...
We're gonna give it all these.
That's for you.
Enjoy.
In fact, I can even give him more, right?
Maybe I can't.
That's fine.
I mean, 60 is plenty for now.
Okay.
Now we glass it.
Wait, wait, so...
It puts that down...
And then it takes one ahead.
Yeah, that sounds right.
How about...
I can't come back then...
Unless I make a little hole for myself.
This machine will work first try when I have it assembled.
There will be no revisions.
Mark my words.
It'll be flawless first time execution here.
Let's not forget...
The lever.
There.
And...
Lock rotation.
There will be no rotating tonight.
Um...
Here, here...
And then one, two, three.
Ah, but then I can't...
This is like a little maintenance tunnel.
Or a shaft.
Or an access thingy.
Like in real tunnels, you know?
They have those.
It's true.
I see that.
Uh...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We can make this even better.
We don't even need glass!
Cause I can just glue the shit, right?
In fact, I'm just gonna do this real quick.
Like that.
And also...
Here.
Now we take the drills.
Just like that.
And now we remove this layer.
Give me that one.
Ah, let me actually put that there.
If you can hear my phone in the background, it's on purpose.
Because I may receive a package and I need to be ready to go grab it.
That's why the phone is not on silent.
I apologize.
It needs to be done.
Okay.
I wonder though if I can make this even more elegant.
So right now it's pretty good.
This is like beautiful, right?
The thing is gonna come in.
It's gonna attach.
And...
Are we good?
Let me check.
It's gonna put down a rail.
It's gonna dig automatically.
Yeah.
I think this is done.
And now...
Oh, wait, wait.
We need to do...
Here.
To...
There.
Here.
To here.
This should all be connected now.
Oh god, I hope.
Wait, it doesn't actually look...
There we go!
Look!
It's all highlighted.
Wait, why is it not highlighted anymore?
It should be good.
You ready?
First try.
Uh, wait.
Let me just double check.
Oh!
Woo!
Almost messed that up.
Okay, so now I push it in.
It's gonna click.
It's gonna plot that down.
And it's gonna...
It's gonna dig.
Here we go!
Yeah!
Wonderful design.
Absolutely beautiful.
Oh!
The chest!
I forgot the chest.
It's fine.
Ah, crap.
Ah, man.
It's fine.
It's okay.
I can pick it up.
I can be the little bitch in the back.
It's picking up the leftovers.
Wait, let me...
Run into you!
There we go.
Give you extra speed.
Oh!
Shit!
Ah!
Uh-oh!
What does it mean?
Okay, it didn't get destroyed.
That's what I thought was gonna happen.
Okay, nice.
This is no problem.
We're actually hard chilling.
We're just gonna get the source taken care of like that.
And this should all be...
Gucci!
Right?
Yeah?
Kinda good to know that it doesn't get destroyed though.
This is some impeccable engineering.
If I do say so myself.
Oh!
I just destroyed my...
blocks there.
This is a long tunnel.
In fact, while that's going away, let's just collect more of these.
Oh, it's kind of dark now.
Let's just feed them.
Here, sir.
Get fed.
Ah!
Wait.
There's actually something wrong here.
Where's the minecart?
Uh...
Wait a second.
Oh, this is not...
Oh, wait a minute.
This is not even animated anymore.
Or simulated.
Oh, I guess the lava does mess you up, huh?
Ah, well.
It is what it is.
In fact, moss!
Hey, I want that!
Maybe I can apply it to my stones.
Make them mossy.
I know there's a way to do it.
I just don't remember how.
Okay, well, I guess the minecart got destroyed.
And my theory on why that is, and not the rest, is that when I used the glue, I actually did it on everything except this block down here.
Which means the minecart wasn't technically part of that, I guess?
So it got destroyed?
Kinda.
I think that makes sense.
Okay, you know what?
Let's use this damn toolbox for something.
Oh yeah, I forgot how much room there is in that.
Wow.
Let's go make another minecart.
In fact, let's also grab stuff from here.
Yeah, I keep forgetting how amazing this toolbox is.
This is unreal.
Gravel is actually something we can use too.
I don't want this nasty coal ore.
Not in that format.
Okay.
We grab another minecart.
Cheers.
And I actually got so much stone now.
I think I'm gonna start blasting it a little bit.
This is like the ultimate way to make your house out of stone.
Digging machine and blaster.
Yo!
We can probably make...
Oh, can we include that in the assembly line?
Imagine blasting that way, assembly line this way.
It comes through and gets blasted.
But maybe you need multiple layers of blasting so they get blasted in time.
Otherwise, we're just gonna run through it real fast, right?
There's a lot of options here.
Okay, minecart.
And the lava situation.
Oh, that's right!
I remember this now.
I had the obsidian idea.
We're gonna encase this in obsidian!
It's so smart!
Do I have any?
Uh...
Miscellaneous?
Honestly, maybe it's not that bad.
As long as I just bring some minecarts...
Like, enough?
What does it take?
Ingots.
I got those.
They don't stack though, so...
That's not so nice.
Let's have three.
For backups.
Yeah.
I like it.
Also, technically, we don't need more than one stack of rails.
Right?
Unless we make some kind of system where the deployer gets fed more rails automatically.
But we're not that lazy, are we?
Not yet, at least.
For now, we're not that lazy.
Let's put them in construction.
There we go.
I got everything else.
Nine drills...
Uh, we don't need this glass anymore.
Just a couple, I guess.
Let me think.
Uh, one...
Two...
You know, we don't need glass, honestly.
What was I thinking?
Let me try this moss block thingy.
Can I make moss now?
It's actually just that simple.
Can I make moss blocks?
Okay, I can make them in this mixer.
But that's not a moss block.
Wait.
I can haunt moss block and it becomes soul soil.
What is that good for, though?
Why would I want to do that?
I don't know yet.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Uh, let's deposit some stone.
Let's actually blast them real quick.
So that means we need lava.
This time I'm not gonna destroy my...
Or turn all my stone bricks into cracked ones.
Okay, so, uh, we need this...
Toolbox...
Here.
Actually, I'm kind of afraid of putting that next to the lava.
Look how crazy this is now.
I'm taking all this cobblestone.
Wait, what can I use...
Diorite on?
Can I do something smart with that?
I can mix diorite and cobblestone!
To get andesite!
Yo!
That's actually massive.
This is plenty.
Diorite is kind of plenty, too.
Like, if I find both of these, I can mix them and turn them into two of them, even.
Whoa.
That's important.
Maybe I'll keep some, then.
And what about andesite itself?
Andesite...
Right, that's this.
Yeah.
Right, you could also mill it.
Andesite and iron.
Yeah, yeah.
But then we also need an automatic way to get iron!
Ooh, hold on, this is...
How the hell do we do that?
Let me think.
Iron.
Right, okay.
Right, that makes sense.
But can I somehow make it out of nothing?
Block of industrial iron and weathered iron.
On the saw.
That one seems more tough, doesn't it?
But I guess with a digging machine, you will pick up some iron?
Um...
Put this in there.
I think that's all I want to blast right now.
Yeah, let's do this.
Blast it!
Show me the goods.
I don't like that this is floating.
We're gonna fix that.
There we go.
That's more like it.
I'm gonna get ready to pick this up.
And...
There we go.
I'm even gonna do this.
Grab it.
And...
Yep, beautiful.
Look at all my stone.
Let's turn some of it into bricks.
Not all of it.
Half of it.
Good!
Okay, so check it out.
We're gonna take one stack, one stack, one stack, one stack.
Let's do a bit of decorating real quick.
Oh!
Yeah, okay.
I'm gonna fill up this path here.
We're gonna have mossy stone here as well in time.
To make it look even more perfect.
It's just the first iteration.
Freaking look at this!
That is beautiful!
And it leads all the way to my house.
Oh, yeah.
One more.
Stack them.
We're gonna make lanterns as well.
Maybe these little lampposts and stuff, you know?
It's gonna be good.
Maybe I'll do the terrace as well.
Let's do it.
This is gonna be stone.
This is where I'm gonna be sitting and enjoying my coffee while I eat my cheese on toast.
In the mornings.
And, of course, the coffee needs to be as dark as a moonless night sky.
Again, first iteration.
We're gonna make this look better in time.
I just wanna get some mossy ones first, you know?
I guess I could use some of this right now.
In fact, maybe I'll also use some normal stones.
Nah.
Make more bricks.
Not bad, huh?
Check it out, man!
Except this one needs to be stoned, too.
No!
There we go.
Wonderful.
Wonderful!
So pretty.
Let's make mossy stuff, right now.
Oh!
We unlocked some- Oh, hold on.
Moss?
Oh, infested mossy stone bricks.
Why would I wanna make that?
I don't understand.
Let me show you my vision here.
Along the edges.
Like this.
Right?
We're gonna do this.
You see?
You see how good that looks?!
Fucking hell, you can't tell me that isn't beautiful.
Cause it's like the grass is, you know, coming on the- The- Okay, that sounded weird.
But it's- You know, it's- It's overlapping.
Basically.
It's a gradient.
Okay!
That's wonderful!
Let me stack my stones.
Here.
And we keep digging!
We're gonna go straight back to digging here.
I'm gonna leave one chest behind.
There you go.
All of this is looking good.
Maybe I keep this here.
Iron ingots was used for the...
carts.
But I don't need them right now.
It's melting.
Oh!
This one we don't need either.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Bow.
So...
Yep.
Okay.
Let's go.
We need a lot of cobblestone- Oh!
By the way.
I know I just turned them all into bricks.
But we need, you know, just cobblestone actually.
There's two of them!
Wait, this bow sucks actually.
Stop!
Oh no.
Without getting hit.
Oh my god, I'm so good.
Oh, we even have an enderman!
And ADP!
Oh, shit.
Oh!
Oh wait, I'm in trouble!
Fucking tech teaming me!
Don't go out at night, kids.
Unless you're me.
I can handle it.
As you saw.
That was actually beautiful.
It was perfection.
Very nice.
Oh, he even came after me.
Didn't even see him.
Yeah, this is gonna get old real fast walking down this tunnel.
We need to find a quick way to travel.
Hmm.
I mean, a minecart obviously is the obvious answer here, but...
I think we can do it faster.
But for now, let's just dig.
And I'm gonna take this moss with me too.
But first, we set up the machine.
Trademark.
Rotten flesh?
We don't need that, actually.
Okay, first, uh...
These.
And then this thing here.
There.
Lever.
Cart.
Boom.
Let's not walk into the cart.
Let's just use some dirt here.
There.
Wait, if I, uh...
Slime all three here.
Is it gonna bring this one along?
I hope not.
Lock rotation.
And...
What next?
The hand.
There.
Remove this.
We don't need it.
Yep.
Oh, we needed the dirt again.
Let me try something new.
Let's not forget the chests, by the way.
Uh, let's put those...
Maybe up here?
Not sure how this is gonna work, but...
Like that?
Now we glue it all together.
Um, you know, I'm scared of...
Frickin' running into this.
Time for the glue.
Oh, get rid of this.
No, I guess I'll do it like this.
Here.
There.
Oh, we broke it.
Good thing I haven't backed up.
Nice.
There.
And then...
Here goes...
Ah, I guess we can do that.
Then from...
Wait, why is that not highlighted correctly?
I can just do that.
But then technically it's gonna...
It's gonna take what's down there, too.
And I don't want that?
Oh, no.
Maybe I do want that.
Maybe it's okay.
You know what?
Let me try something.
Take the top part here.
Bring it to here, and then from here to there.
It's taking these andesites, but maybe that's okay.
I don't know if that's okay.
Let's find out, shall we?
Here we go.
Oh, oh!
There we go.
Okay, here we go.
Ultimate digging.
Activate.
And while that's digging, I'm gonna collect this.
Maybe with my hole.
Oh, yeah.
Even better.
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
This is efficiency, people.
My stuff is working while I'm working.
Now we need this, and that.
Dude, I'm gonna have mossy cobblestone for YEARS after this!
I wonder if my digging machine is still going.
I'm surprised there's no monsters here.
Why didn't the digging machine kill these guys?
Wait, what happened back here?
Is it just... oh.
No!
My digging machine!
Where'd you go?!
Oh, yeah, we...
Ah, this is a real mess.
Guys, this is fucked.
Oh, man.
We gotta figure out how to optimize this, because this is not ideal right now.
It just ain't...
It's gone, man.
Oh, shit.
That digging machine is in Africa.
Wait, is it still digging down there?
I wonder.
It got momentum from the water?
Maybe it's going on its merry way.
Think about it.
I got a lot of moss, too.
In fact, let me fill up my toolbox.
No, I left it behind!
Ah...
I can't believe I've done this.
This water is gonna really be annoying.
It's fine, though.
Let's find this digging machine.
Oh, there it is!
It's not even destroyed.
We got invaders, though.
Can't have that.
Oh, there's a bowman on the right.
Uh, so I guess the water kinda destroyed it.
Or, can I push it still?
Oh, wait, I don't have a shield.
Gotta have the shield for this.
There we go.
Light the path.
Oh, man, that water is just annoying.
I wonder if I can...
Hold on.
Can I do something with my wrench, maybe?
Is this even simulated anymore?
Wait, yeah, it's definitely simulated.
Hmm.
There's gotta...
What I'm thinking is, there's gotta be, like, a way to...
Make this unsimulated, you know?
Without having to use the damn...
What is that?
Oh, it's a fish.
Without using the...
Assembly thingy.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
The chest opened.
Hey, look, it works!
Everything's in there!
Jesus.
Very nice.
Hmm.
I'm not taking damage when I walk into it.
Uh, this should still be digging, by the way, if I push it.
But I don't think I can because of the water.
Maybe I need to use glue on it first?
No, you gotta use the thing.
Also, let me get rid of this water.
Let's find the source.
Oh, there's multiple sources.
Yeah, that's amazing.
Wait, how am I gonna get this out of here?
Give me...
Wait, where's the...
Oh!
Is that what was wrong?
Are you free now?
Push!
Wait, do I even want it to dig, though?
I don't want it to dig yet.
Oh, my God.
I gotta go grab the frickin' assembly thingy.
This is...
We gotta find a way to prevent falling into holes.
And we gotta have some kind of cover up top that's...
It's like hydrophobic.
And also, uh...
Lavaphobic.
We hate lava.
Also, since I'm here...
Grab this...
You know what I need?
I need a, uh...
Like a graviton weapon.
Something that can be like...
Move my machine up here again, you know what I mean?
Uh, no!
It's gone.
Okay, whatever.
So, obviously, this water is gonna fuck me.
Um...
We're gonna have to try...
We have to stop the source.
There's no other way.
Either that, or make...
Yeah, actually, we can also just make the tunnel.
Wait, why are you not coming down here?
Yeah, you can't escape the current sun.
Good luck.
Neither can I, apparently.
Good.
Okay, let's just do this.
Oh, God.
Stop!
Stop it!
Why is the water still in here?
I don't understand that.
Like, the water should be gone from in here.
Water physics in Minecraft make no sense.
It is the most unintuitive thing of all time.
Oh, I finally did something, maybe?
Oh, my God.
This is painful!
Stop the source!
I'm losing my mind.
No more.
It's probably just a single block somewhere messing up my life.
What's up, bro?
Don't mind me.
It's this little...
This little asshole there!
Show's over!
No more.
I'm gonna kill you.
You're dead, son.
I don't need an EDP.
Oi!
Come on!
Brother.
Oi!
Okay.
Come on!
Get up here.
There we go.
Give me your pearl.
Thank you.
Let's stop the other water.
Because I'm not done.
I'm on a mission to stop all the water in the world.
We don't like water.
I hate water!
Wait, did I...
Wait, how did I just...
Stop the water?
Where?
Did I just put a block accidentally where the water source was?
And where...
Wait, what?
I don't even see the dirt!
Like...
I'm so confused.
I'm sorry, fishes.
You're all gonna die.
We also have this water up here that needs to die.
There's a skeleton somewhere.
Oh, you wanna...
Piece of me?
Boom.
Like, in all this time it takes me to...
To...
Perform maintenance on this machine, I could've gathered more materials myself.
Maybe.
This is how inefficient it is to have these...
Unexpected...
Problems!
Shit!
Yeah, shoot each other.
Dumbasses.
That's what I like to see.
Oh!
They pushed the cart!
That's funny.
I didn't know they could do that.
Alright, give me...
Give me the thingies.
Thank you.
We're gonna put this...
There.
Good.
Okay.
Uh, and the way this works...
It's off now, so if I push it should just...
There we go.
Wonderful.
That's probably an easy way of doing this.
Somehow, someway.
Um...
I...
There's also something else.
Like, yes, there's items in these boxes now.
But...
How am I gonna get it home?
Uh...
Hmm.
Maybe there's a way to somehow...
Simulate the boxes and maybe drag them home with a rope?
You know how Santa does it with his presents in the back?
Maybe that's me later with the chests, you know?
I don't know.
Uh, in any case, we need to disassemble this.
I'm at the chests, though.
Oh, no.
Oh, man.
This is hell.
And there's still water!
Oh.
Okay, hold on.
We're not done.
Also, I need to sleep.
Enemies are spawning!
Thank you.
Now.
Let's go stop the water, once and for all, so it cannot bother us anymore.
I have a feeling this is from a lake.
Come on.
All in...
Just to make...
An assembly line, you know?
It's a whole thing.
Okay, let's stop the lake here.
Let's use...
Stone.
Because it's aesthetic.
Wonderful.
What a nice lake.
What is that up there?
Oh, it...
Wait!
That's also a way to get mossy cobblestone, I guess.
Let's go collect it.
Okay.
Oh, wait!
Dude, I have an idea.
Uh...
Actually, it's my idea of blocking holes, but like...
Taken to the extreme.
I need...
One, two...
Three, four...
Five, six...
I need eight deployers.
Give me eight deployers and I can do anything.
You'll see what I mean.
I heard a skeleton.
Maybe we just leave these items here for now.
They're not gonna go anywhere.
I know where they are.
My inventory is a mess.
Throw away some stuff.
Drip leaf?
No thanks.
Don't want that.
Stop!
I guess I kinda want this for my house.
Yeah.
That's fine.
Let's take these home.
But the question is, if I use my glue now, is it still gonna...
Yeah, that's the weird thing, you know?
Get rid of it.
Where's my...
axe?
Wait, what?
Am I blind?
What the hell is my axe?
That makes no sense.
Don't need that.
I'll take some cobblestone.
And... copper.
Yeah, it's gone.
Axe is gone.
Disappeared off the face of the earth.
Who knows what happened to it?
Nobody knows.
It is a mystery.
I got everything that's important.
Oh!
The axe is right here.
Haha.
Nice.
That makes me feel better.
Very good.
Okay.
I'm gonna make my frickin' mega ultra...
Monstro machine now.
It needs, in total, nine deployers.
And it needs...
a shit ton of blocks.
Which kind?
It doesn't matter.
It just needs...
It's gonna be crazy.
Now you may ask yourself...
Oliver, why nine?
Because we have eight on the outside, and one more...
for the rails!
Dummy!
Right?
You see the vision?
Imagine like a...
uh...
18...
times...
4...
almost a hundred...
fingered machine.
Okay?
Even though it's just a pointing finger, there's also the thumb.
And we have all the other fingers too.
But is it expensive to make a deployer?
Ooh!
That's really expensive!
Okay, you know what?
Before I go crazy with the...
you know...
almost a hundred finger machine...
maybe we just stick to one, to see if it even works.
Yeah.
Let's do that, shall we?
Electron tube, do I have it?
I don't possess it.
God dammit.
It takes...
uh...
polished rose quartz, I probably don't have that either.
But to make that, we just need to rub it a little bit.
As they say.
Uh...
Let me make a bunch of moss, since I'm here.
What do I not need right now?
Maybe this one.
I have six of these now, we can soon kill the dragon!
Uh...
Oh!
Let's put these down.
Just to get them out of the inventory.
Hey, look at that!
Wonderful!
Alright.
We also have a salia.
Let's just have some more.
Look at that!
That's wonderful, isn't it?
Maybe even some near the windows.
Maybe one up here.
One there.
Here.
Ah, maybe not there.
I hate that there.
Oh yes.
Look!
At the beauty.
Also, I need to find my phone.
One sec.
Okay.
Nothing important.
Right.
Dude, this house is starting to come together, isn't it?
I mean, look at this out here.
Let's make some mossy cobble.
Can I make mossy cracked?
Oops, I took something I shouldn't have.
Mossy.
60.
I'm gonna do it right now.
This is gonna look so good.
Gimme!
I got it.
Oh my god.
It actually looks insane.
Wow!
Like, it's tiny, right?
But it adds so much.
It's very subtle.
But it's important.
Oh yeah.
We're also gonna do it out here.
Near the edge, of course.
Maybe we even have one sneaking into the center like that, you know?
Maybe some of them get over here like that.
Maybe here.
It's not maintained all the way, right?
Because we're a little lazy.
Now, can I make mossy cracked?
I don't think so, but I can make this.
That's kind of exciting.
Ew!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Dude!
Yo!
Oh, but then it looks shit from inside.
Oh.
Maybe flapjacks to the rescue on the inside?
Nobody will know.
We're doing it.
We're going all in with this.
Oh my god, yes.
Oh yes, that's so good.
And over here too.
Oh yes.
Look!
Oh wait, actually it doesn't make sense here, does it?
But what does make sense, is to maybe add a bit of this, here and there, you know, to mix it up a bit.
We could even add some mossy ones there.
Going into non-mossy ones.
Uh, here.
Here.
You see?
Not bad.
In fact, maybe I'll just sprinkle in some...
stones like that.
You know?
Not bad at all.
It looks a little funky, but...
It's part of the charm, you know?
The house is like...
imperfect.
And that's the whole...
that's the whole draw of it.
All this mossy stuff.
Let's put it in here.
All this stone.
Well, the good news is, we have a bunch of cobblestone now, that we can use...
for the assembly line project.
That is ultimately what I'm trying to do here, right?
But, first, we needed to make the...
ultimate Mega Man machine...
thingy.
So we needed the ployer, which needed the...
brass hand, and electron tube.
And electron tube we needed to polish.
So...
where's that?
Polish...
There.
Sandpaper.
And to make the...
brass...
I'm guessing we need brass.
Yeah.
Andesite alloy too.
In fact, let's just make a bunch of that.
For the future.
Let's make five.
Yep.
In.
And for the tube, I believe we needed...
quartz...
exo...
No wait, was it just redstone dust?
And... and quartz?
Hold on, is my memory actually impeccable?
Impeccable?
Let me see, uh...
quartz...
OH MY GOD!
I'm amazing.
And now?
Offhand?
Boom.
Rubbing it.
Oh, durability goes down fast.
Ah!
Crap.
But that's easy to make, right?
Oh, sand and paper.
It makes so much sense.
It's crazy.
That's it.
We got six of them now.
Good.
Then we need iron sheets.
I'm actually just gonna make six of them.
Now, next up, uh, it was...
uh, the hand we had already.
Deployer, we also need it.
Andesite casing.
Where would I have put that?
Cause I know I have some.
Is it just in create?
It is indeed.
I'm gonna make one.
We're gonna test it first.
See if it even works.
Otherwise, there's no point.
The rest looks...
good.
So, for my test, we're gonna need some...
Well, whatever we have.
Could use basalt.
Doesn't really matter.
Actually, no.
I'd rather just use...
a stack of cobblestone.
And I think I'm ready.
Nothing else I need, right?
We got the tube.
Okay.
So, check it.
We are gonna do a...
So, remember when I said...
walls and grommet?
In terms of rails?
We're gonna do the same thing, but with stone.
In front of the rails.
The only issue I have is...
what if there's like a hole of two or plus more, you know?
That's the problem right now.
In fact, I'm gonna try it right here.
Um...
In fact, we don't need to make the whole machine.
We just need to sort of...
make something super simple.
Lock that.
Well, how do I wanna do this?
I guess I can...
I guess we would have to figure out what the range is of the deployer.
Let me put it like this for now.
That's a little close, but...
Ah, wait.
We need two of them, actually.
Yeah, that's fine, that's fine.
So here.
And there.
And now the trick is...
On this one, we're gonna give it rails.
Why can't I do that?
Oh, there we go.
And on this one, we're gonna give it a bunch of stone, right?
If my theory is right, this is gonna fill up at least this one for sure.
This is gonna work.
It's gonna fill this up.
Um...
And maybe also this one, even though it's two blocks down, because we don't know what the range is on this, but it's definitely more than one block, I guess.
The problem is, what if there's a hole with like, 50?
Then we're screwed, right?
Unless we put the thing while pointing at this side of the block before it!
Wait a second, I actually...
Oh, this is it!
We have to sort of make it...
Let's just test this first.
Before we go too crazy.
So, it's locked.
This is gonna go in.
Remove that one.
Let's try it!
Ah!
I forgot!
I forgot something.
No, go back in.
What is happening?
Oh, I hate this!
I forgot how I had it set up now as well.
Wait, why is that?
Oh, it got moved one.
Here.
There.
There we go.
Now, glue...
Wait, is this one part of it now?
Or...
No, that should be fine.
That should be fine.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let me just double check.
It's gonna...
Let's see.
Why didn't it, uh...
Wait, what the fuck is going on?
Push it back in.
There we go.
Okay.
Now...
What is the problem here?
I think this one may need to be one higher.
Ah, shit.
I think maybe it's too close.
Let me also un-glue this.
That's for you.
And...
Ah, but now I'm really unsure about this down here.
Wait.
Oh!
Here?
Maybe it...
Maybe I shouldn't do the thing in front of the thingies.
So we go like this, and then from here...
There.
That's it.
You ready?
Here we go.
Ah, sh...
Okay, okay, okay.
I guess that makes sense.
That actually makes a lot of sense.
That is to be expected, honestly.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Back, back on, back on.
There we go.
This one needs to be one lower.
Of course it does!
Oh, yeah, that makes so much sense.
It needs to be like that.
Yeah.
So now...
Here you go.
Now it can't put down until it goes here, then it can.
Right?
Okay, you ready?
No, just...
God, this minecart is driving me crazy.
Also, are we still...
We're not glued.
Unglue!
Stop!
This gluing system is so confusing.
There we go!
Here we go.
You ready?
It's gonna work.
Move!
Oh!
It's...
How does...
Wait, what?
How?
What the fuck?
It's going through the rock!
But hey, we got it figured out!
So I guess the way it works, it simply looks at this face instead of down, which is...
Actually, you know what?
It kind of makes sense.
Although not really.
Think about it like this.
I am now the deployer, okay?
I am Mr. D.
Mr. D comes running like this, you know?
I go...
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't...
Oh wait, let me make a bigger hole.
But imagine like, he's right clicking so fast, Mr. D is coming in so fast, that when he's right on this pixel, he actually manages to target the side of the block here.
Before it actually looks down.
Do you see what I mean?
It's coming like this, I go slow.
Okay, there I didn't manage to do it, but...
I guess it's like so mechanically accurate that it just, you know, it happens to target that...
face before it even hits the bottom face.
Do you know what I mean by that?
That's pretty much how that works, I think.
Um, you're still somehow rolling, that's impressive.
Can you stop?
What if I unglue you...
Hold on, there's gotta be...
Let me try this again.
Hold on, let me actually read about...
This.
When used on contraptions, relocates assembled minecart and train-based contraptions!
But it doesn't do that.
Wait.
Why didn't that work before?
Relocates assembled minecart and...
No, it doesn't.
Wait.
Huh?
I'm so confused.
No, it doesn't.
It fucking destroyed the minecart.
It didn't relocate shit.
But I'm glad there's some kind of way to do it without the...
card assembly every time.
At least it's gonna be easier to...
relocate it...
manually.
Okay, well this actually kinda solves everything.
Except...
We actually need eight more deployers.
Wait, do we do...
Hold on, do we need eight?
Yeah, we do need eight.
We need eight.
Actually?
I think.
One, two, three...
Oh, wait.
We actually need...
12.
We need 12 deployers.
13 in total.
Yeah, that's a lot of deployers.
Damn, that's a lot.
Hmm.
Do I have 12 deployers?
Let me see.
Yeah, I need 12.
No, 13.
Yeah, 13.
But we already have some, so it's...
We gotta go make some deployers.
Hmm, wait.
I wonder...
If we do it sideways?
How that's gonna work.
Hold on.
Quick test.
Let's do...
We don't even need, um...
We're just gonna do it like this.
Yeah.
Boink!
Oh, I can't just glue one.
I guess that makes sense.
Fine.
I'll glue two.
I need to see what happens here.
We're just experimenting right now.
Ah, obviously this is not gonna work.
Ah, it's gonna fall down and it's...
Oh, wait.
But then...
Let's relocate it.
Or...
We just turn it, actually.
And what is the best test case here?
Maybe...
Maybe here.
There.
Uh...
Let me think.
There.
Here.
One more, I guess.
I'm gonna need to have the rails, you know?
It's gonna be part of it.
There's no way around it.
Like that.
Now we give you some rails.
And then, next to this one, we're gonna have this guy.
Oh, look at this!
You can even exp...
Oh!
Cool!
This sort of windmill system works here too.
Oh.
I don't want it that way.
But can...
I can do that and then I can use the thing.
Did I just close the...
Hand?
Look at that!
There we go.
That's the way I wanted it.
Now, stone.
Glue.
It's gonna be crazy.
Let's see.
Sick.
Basically, I wanna see how this works that way.
Because it was very unintuitive the way it worked that way just now.
So I need to see what happens here.
Whoops.
No.
Remove it.
Okay.
Here we go.
On.
And...
Oh, wait.
It's not gonna drill so it'll need to stop after a while.
I don't want it to go off into infinity.
Let's do that.
What the fuck?!
That makes no sense.
That is not how right-click works for me.
If I just do this in mid-air...
It's not placing any blocks.
So it's not a direct copy of the player...
As I thought it was.
Now I know how this works down here.
It is actually not targeting the side of the thing.
Because it is not consistent with the player.
It is its own thing.
Basically what it does is...
It always places the thing...
Two blocks ahead.
No matter what.
It doesn't need to attach it to something else.
It just does it.
This is great news!
For my 13-deployer setup.
That's exactly what I needed.
Let me try this thing again now.
So if I...
There's no way that worked.
Oh my god!
Guys, that is exactly what I meant when I set...
Uh...
Like a...
Gravity thingy to just...
Pick it up and go...
You know?
That is fantastic.
Why...
So, okay.
Something that is very confusing...
I tried this two other times.
With different results.
Because I figured there's gotta be a way to...
Not have destroyed every time.
And freaking put it on this, you know?
Like, I know there's gotta be a way.
So it's gotta be the wrench, right?
It's always the wrench.
The problem is, the first time...
Nothing happened.
Like, I clicked everywhere.
Second time, I destroyed the minecart!
Third time it worked.
Maybe it was the water that interfered?
I don't know.
Oh wait, it's still simulated though.
So how do I make it just not...
Oh, I must have left clicked.
Okay, okay, okay.
I understand.
I think.
But the water thing is still a little confusing.
I must have left clicked the second time.
Yeah, that makes sense actually.
It's starting to make a lot of sense.
Okay, uh...
We need a lot of deployers now.
Because I'm gonna show you.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Hmm.
Maybe I need a little detector system set up.
So...
Basically, I can make a way for it to go...
Oh, I see something.
Therefore, I don't do it.
Ah, there's no way to know for sure though.
Unless I have an outer layer of observers.
Wait, what happens to an observer if it's simulated and it's moving into...
a populated block from a non-populated block?
Is that gonna matter?
Hmm...
I don't know.
Uh...
Whoa, wait!
Does it work with the chests though?
Where's my chests at?
Did I leave...
Wait, did I leave those at home?
I don't know.
I must have left them at home.
Ah, wait, no, no, no!
They're down here, dude!
One of them is still full!
So all I need to...
So, if I connect it to the minecart...
Via the minecart assembly.
And I just pick it up.
Because it's gonna be part of it, right?
Because it's glued.
That should work.
This feels like cheating now.
I'm gonna fill up these holes.
That's fine.
That's a maintenance tunnel.
Man, I talk a lot here!
Wow!
I'm practically running forever.
Okay, there they are.
Let's see if I can...
Um...
Let me think.
Read this again.
Relocate, assemble minecart, and train?
Dude!
I feel like I need to shift focus completely and make a train right fucking now.
I want a train so bad!
Anyway, let me quickly do this.
So, we would have to do it like this.
Or maybe we don't.
Can I just...
Oh, okay.
Wait, what?
Place your cart assemble on a rail block?
But it said something else just now.
It said ore, and then something else.
But...
It disappeared, I don't know.
Just for test.
Ah, wait.
We need power.
Orientation doesn't matter.
Oh, my...
God!
Whoa, there's no way, dude.
So wait, isn't this just a way to transport, like, infinite amounts of items?
I feel like I'm just kind of breaking the game here.
This doesn't feel allowed.
Feels illegal, you know what I mean?
Wow.
Like, let's say I want to relocate my base.
I fucking pick up everything.
Into my little magic rucksack.
And take it with me.
Wow.
I mean, okay.
At first it was the bulk blasting that kinda made me think, okay...
I can just do anything, you know?
Like, I don't even need fuel anymore.
I can just put that stuff in there and it'll just immediately get blasted.
That sounded insane to me.
That's nothing compared to this.
Why...
Why am I allowed to do this?
I feel like I...
I wouldn't have allowed that if I made this mod.
I didn't make the mod, but if I had...
I wouldn't have allowed that.
That seems kinda crazy.
Let me see here.
If I... if I now do...
Can I just put it anywhere?
Like...
Let me put it here.
I may have to be on rails, I guess?
And now I just go like this?
Tell me that isn't insane.
Wow.
Okay.
I guess it is kinda cumbersome to do, in the moment, but you know...
Still.
We definitely need a greenery box.
Am I right?
We should do that now.
Yeah, let's make a sign unless I have it already.
I don't.
Sticks.
And you know what, actually?
I'm gonna go get some...
Oak.
Normal oak for this.
And the reason is, the dark oak signs...
It's actually kinda hard to read the text on it.
Because the sign is so dark.
And the text is dark, right?
So we're gonna switch over to oak signs.
Oh, that's the next...
Oh, I should bring my hand crank.
I don't have it.
That's too bad.
The hand crank is the solution to ugly trees.
Just like mustard gas is the solution.
I'm not gonna...
Oh, that was so funny.
I was about to say orphans, but...
I don't know, I feel like that could be understood out of context, you know?
Honestly, anything with orphans can be...
I mean, a fucking orphan crusher, you know?
What... I mean, orphan crushing and orphan gassing?
Is it really, you know, we're...
Does it matter at that point?
I don't know.
Oh shit, not the ugly tree.
Hold on, I need the...
axe.
The axe I thought I had lost, but now I have it.
Okay.
Let's take one more.
That should be enough.
Okay.
I'm definitely gonna make an orphan blaster, though.
That one is...
That's a home run, I think.
Or...
You know, honestly?
Do we even need to blast the orphans when we can just smoke them?
You know?
We smoke them and put them on a barbe.
I mean, apparently I take damage from it, so why wouldn't enemies, right?
It's genius.
Alright, let's make oak planks.
Oh, I was about to say, did I only get that?
But no, I got more.
How many signs can I make?
Oh, I get three!
Every time!
Okay, that's good.
That's very good.
I'm gonna replace all of these.
Wood.
Smelting.
Oh, no.
Wood.
Stone.
Create.
No.
Yeah, I'll run out.
Redstone.
Exotic.
Kinda wanna reuse the category names I had in the...
in the other one.
Coal!
No.
Construction.
Miscellaneous.
God, I'm good.
Okay, and then we have equipment.
Can we please run out soon?
Damn it.
Let's make a greenery here.
Or, just green.
And I think we may need a second create.
Let me rename this one.
No.
We can have it here.
Create two.
The long awaited successor.
Put all the wood in here.
Honestly, this is looking good.
Sixteen.
Times the signs.
Clayball?
I don't know where that belongs.
I would say miscellaneous.
Yeah.
No more greens.
I forgot what I was doing.
I honestly have no idea what I'm doing right now.
Why am I here?
What is my name?
Uh...
Wait, what was I doing?
I was...
Okay, I was...
I was digging.
Oh, right!
Twelve deployers.
Hands and tubes.
Thank you.
We have five now.
That's it?
I feel like we should have more.
Maybe I put them in the create box.
Oh wait, I didn't use all my electron tubes.
Ah.
So what is the current...
limitation?
Casings.
Damn casings!
Oh, I guess we need a farming box as well.
Put it next to the green box.
Farming.
Put all the seeds and stuff in there, you know?
Seeds.
Then we have green.
God, my inventory is horrible!
Fix it!
I'm gonna keep these because I need them.
That's definitely miscellaneous.
Coal is in here.
Yeah.
Farming.
Oh god, I hate this fucking inventory management.
There's gotta be like an easy way to do this with create.
We're gonna figure it out in time.
It's coming.
Oh, it's coming.
I would say sugarcane is farming.
Maybe wheat as well.
Yeah, actually.
What else is farming here?
I would almost say bone meal, but that's pushing it.
Mushrooms are green.
Some of them.
And we need a food box.
I have some food in here.
I don't even know what to do with a tropical fish.
Maybe there's something to do with it in create.
Because this is the most useless item in Minecraft.
Maybe next to the potato.
The rotten potato, you know.
The Minecraft developer actually told me straight to my face that that is an item that has absolutely no uses in the game.
And I have never forgotten ever since.
And I wonder why.
You know.
Why is it in here?
It's a question.
Okay.
This is food.
Food, food.
Toot, toot.
And alloys.
We actually need those.
Now we need more tubes.
Which means we need redstone.
Which I don't have?
No way.
What?
I must have redstone.
We have some there.
Oh, oh, oh.
We have 26 blocks of it.
Okay, yeah.
I was about to say.
Just two of them.
And then we need the exotic stuff.
The good stuff.
16 Quartz's.
And now we're gonna rub it so hard.
We could even make a deployer do this, by the way.
Yeah, we need more sandpaper.
But I don't have any paper.
Sugar cane.
Look, it's already paying off.
Kinda.
Ah, we need one more sugar cane!
No way.
Wait, but I can make paper in some other way, right?
Wait.
Hey, yeah!
Hell yeah!
We can make two!
Easy.
Bonk them!
Oh yeah.
One more.
Yoink!
Dude, we can make a factory that produces...
Ultimate end goal is to have one chest for every item in the game.
One chest for everything.
Which means we're gonna have over a thousand chests.
The ultimate factory.
Maybe that's a bit too much.
Let's calm down.
Sand...
Oh, we need sand, of course.
Now that we have the paper.
Sand is in stone.
Dup, dup.
How did I even this...
How did I spell it that way?
Plus popper!
Sometimes I don't understand how I hit the keyboard that way.
Here we go.
Rub it.
And then we need brass hands, so we need more brass.
Especially the flattened brass.
And brass I forgot how to make.
We'll have to see.
Brass.
Copper and zinc.
Right, okay.
We can go blast this, I guess.
Yeah, let's actually do that.
That means we need lava.
Show me the bucket.
I love this little blasting operation I've got going here.
Anything else I need to blast while I'm here?
I don't think so.
I forgot what I was blasting.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, so now that we do that, we're going to need to have...
What was it?
I actually have some of that, I think.
Wait a minute.
Dude, look at my bo...
Why is this...
You see the little effect?
Why is this yellow?
On my dirt, look.
I don't know.
What does that mean?
Did I click...
Did I do something?
Oh, well.
Whatever.
I need zinc.
Only have six.
Oh, but I do have a bunch of ingots.
Sweet.
Brass.
I need it...
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it was the other book.
It's the only way to do it with mixing?
I guess it is.
We need some power for the blaze burner.
Unless it's already going.
Can't see from here.
Let's just bring it some.
Got two cools it can have.
Sink.
Copper.
Let's do it.
Are you happy down there?
I don't think you're happy.
I can make you happy.
Okay, now...
Copper.
Zinc.
What's this?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, that's fine.
Man, I hate having to unsubscribe from pretty much...
Everyone who messages me, you know?
I freaking hate the unsubscribe culture on emails.
It's just horrible.
Especially if there's no button to do it at the bottom of the email and you have to write them back.
Pisses me off.
Okay, this is gonna take a while, I guess.
Let me go sleep.
Can I take some already?
I don't need a lot.
Why did it take the copper ingots?
Huh?
Is it because my inventory is full?
Ah, it was, okay.
We're not done yet.
Let's put these in.
Okay, with brass in hand.
We can make a hand.
Ah!
They need to be pressed!
See, this is why we need a production line, you know?
But it's obviously easier...
Oh.
Oh, okay, I could just throw it on there.
Good.
It's easier said than done, obviously.
Because you can say this about almost anything so far.
Oh, we need a production line for that, right?
And it's not so easy to just set my whole ass lineup.
Thank you.
That's gonna take a while.
Now let me think.
For the deployer, there was one more thing I needed.
And you know what?
It's good to make all these deployers anyway.
If we're gonna have production lines.
Andesite casings.
That's right.
Which means we need wood.
Oh my god, this inventory is just...
It's ugly.
It's so terrible.
Also, what is in my box?
Oh, it's outside, isn't it?
Let me go get that.
There you are.
Oh my goodness.
You're coming with me.
Uh...
Oh my fucking god.
Ah!
Hate it.
What do I do?
I'm losing my mind.
Okay, one thing at a time.
Sandpaper.
Do we need it?
We do need it.
Not anymore.
We're done with that.
Okay.
Nether quartz.
In here.
One thing at a time.
Redstone I put in.
Good.
Sticks?
Who cares?
Not me.
We also don't need all these arrows.
Brass ingots we need.
Actually, we don't.
Because we're gonna make some right now.
Some sheets.
I'll take the ones I need.
No, stop.
We're gonna press those.
Now that I have these.
We can make brass.
Hand!
Okay.
Don't have enough andesites.
Oh no!
Did I run out?
Wait, no I didn't.
Maybe it's just really expensive.
Yeah, it needs a lot of sheets.
Okay.
Let's make this with wood now.
Ah, wait.
It needs to be stripped wood.
Doesn't it?
Uh, stripped.
Do I have any?
I don't.
Okay.
I have seven now.
Oh, I forgot to make the tubes.
Huh.
That's just iron sheets.
Gonna make ten.
And then the rest we're gonna put in here.
Uh, tube.
No.
Deployer.
Ten.
We need three more.
There you go.
Four hands.
Thirteen!
We did it!
I'm just gonna collect the remaining here for good measure.
I think it's one more.
We done?
We're done.
Oh man, I love this path.
I don't love that though.
Let's get rid of that.
No!
Don't get distracted.
Focus on the thirteen deployers.
The problem is...
The thirteen deployers need to only deploy for as long as I say go.
I need to keep a lookout and disengage it in time.
This is the problem with the thirteen deployers.
I'll show you what I mean.
First though, let's empty this.
And I'm actually gonna take some back in a second here.
Uh, we definitely need a stone too.
Running out of space.
I'm carrying around this hoe.
Maybe it's not worth it.
The boat is also not worth it.
Or the bed.
The rest is worth it.
I need to go pee though.
We are back.
Back.
You know, I had the thought that...
So Jackie, normally when I'm done streaming, Jackie will come running into my room to start playing, right?
She knows I'm done, so now it's time to play and eat.
I wonder if she's gonna do the same now that we're in this new apartment.
It's kind of a fun little experiment to see whether or not her perception and habits have transferred over now that she's in a new environment.
You know what I mean?
It'll be interesting to see.
Anyway, um...
I'm gonna grab this with me.
And I think it's time!
It's time to present to you my magnum opus.
At least my small magnum opus.
We also don't need three minecarts, honestly.
Not with this setup that I've got going here.
Um...
I don't know where to put the minecart.
It doesn't really belong anywhere.
Maybe equipment, actually.
So for this, we're gonna need a lot of stone.
When this baby hits 88 miles per hour, you're gonna see some serious shit.
Let's not use the important blocks here.
Dirt is not that important.
But...
No, it's... yeah, it's okay.
Actually, I need this dirt.
Maybe some deep slate and some basalt and...
this and...
that.
Maybe...
a bit of diorite, a bit of...
No, not andesite.
Very important.
Yeah, I mean cobblestone is plenty.
I'm gonna get so much of it.
It's fine.
In fact, I don't have enough.
Give me diorite.
Fill it up.
In fact, we take almost everything.
Because we're gonna get so much more out of this.
Okay.
Let's see.
We got glue.
We got nine drills.
We got thirteen deployers.
We got the card assembler.
We got the lever.
We got everything we need.
Even got the wrench.
Oh, wait.
Good measure.
There we go.
In fact, let's have that...
here.
My pickaxe is about to break!
I should fix that before I go.
Um...
I'll need stone...
No, uh...
Iron for that, I think?
Crap.
I may not have enough.
Uh-oh.
In fact, maybe I'll bring my other pickaxe.
Yeah.
Temporary pickaxe.
We don't need the hole.
So...
Put it here.
The shovel we do need...
We don't need the brass hand!
That's good!
Are you ready?
This is gonna blow your mind.
I present to you...
My...
Uh...
What do you call it?
Rail laying...
Stone path laying...
And...
Lava...
Immune...
And water immune...
Digging machine.
It's going to be sick.
It is completely immune to everything, if my theory is correct.
Who's messaging me?
It's my dad.
Cheers.
I really hope they make that delivery today, otherwise Jackie's gonna go hungry.
It's her food, you know?
If there's no delivery day, there's no food for Jackie.
They better be arriving with that soon.
Uh, let me make it here.
Also, I'm kidding, of course.
She does have some food left.
Come on.
I would never...
You know, keep it...
Or...
Have it be that close.
I need these here.
We need a little maintenance tunnel.
That is a must.
Actually, hold on.
This is gonna be...
Kind of a big one.
Let me make a little nice...
Excavation here.
Otherwise...
It's not really gonna work.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here we go.
That goes there.
Then we're gonna put one of these here.
Lever, of course.
Actually, I should've put this one further back.
Lever here.
And...
We're gonna make sure this is locked.
Now comes the ultimate...
Contraption.
Give me stone.
Salt.
Dirt.
Okay.
Now I need to think.
First things first.
We're gonna have a hand that places...
Rails.
Put the rails in before we forget.
Boom.
Now.
Now it's gonna be exciting.
Now I need to think.
We actually have a problem already...
That I can see.
Unless we just make it bigger than it is.
But that's not...
Actually, that is gonna work.
Oh, I guess it's just gonna be bigger on the outside...
Than it is on the inside.
Yeah.
That's fine.
But!
First.
How did I do this before?
Oh yeah, I did this.
No, no!
Wait, whoa!
There we go.
Here.
Then we need...
This guy.
This is for making sure that there's room, right?
To put the rail...
It's gonna put two blocks ahead, so...
Wait.
Yeah.
Two blocks ahead, so...
What?
Two.
Right there.
Yeah, this is good.
Okay.
But now...
We're also...
Gonna have...
A hand that goes up.
Alright?
Oh, we just don't have room for this.
Oh no.
This is gonna be a mess.
This is like trying to build a train station in a phone booth.
It's gonna be a problem.
Uh...
What is it, Jackie?
Are you jumping up?
Come here.
Um...
Oh, I guess...
I guess we can just use this wrench...
To fix mistakes.
How can I make you...
Point up?
Huh?
Oh!
I just...
I picked it up just now.
Oh, right.
You can do that.
I don't know if you can hear Jackie in the background.
She is...
Making lots of cat noises.
Yeah, we actually need this too.
There we go!
It's pointing up.
Now I need you not to do that.
Yes!
Very nice.
Not good.
Oh no!
Not again.
Jackie, please.
You cannot do this.
There's hairs everywhere if you do that.
Give me that.
Oh man, this is a mess.
Guys, I don't know how to do this.
I am so bad at intuiting how these hands are gonna move.
Oh, I can even do that, huh?
Really?
That's nice.
Yeah, this is gonna point down.
But maybe that's okay, actually.
Yeah, that is okay.
That's what I want.
Yes, this is what I want.
In fact, this guy needs to go away.
Look at the way they're sort of competing.
Right there.
I don't like the look of that.
We're gonna block it.
Nobody gets to see that.
I do not want you pointing down.
Wrong way again.
Can you please just point the right way?
Maybe this way?
No?
Fuck!
Rotate it!
Why are you going every way I need you?
This is so not intuitive for me at all.
Please just go the one way I want you to go.
There we go!
I don't know how I did it, but I did.
Finally.
Good.
Yes.
Oh no, I right-click on it.
There we go.
Now we need three on this side too.
The remaining three I have.
We're gonna block this.
Let me see.
Nice.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
That's how you do it, baby.
And this zombie is annoying me.
Come here, sucker.
I see you up there.
I'm gonna put some lights in your face.
Get away from me.
There.
No more shenanigans.
I need to double check everything about this contraption before we start this bad boy.
This is good though.
Oh my god, it's sexy.
It's so good.
I present to you...
The machine hole maker.
But also tunnel maker.
All in one.
We're gonna give you 60.
No!
Stop it.
There we go.
There.
Here.
This is gonna be immune to lava, water, and everything else.
It's gonna maintain perfect shape on the tunnel.
It is a work of art.
Look at this.
Now the top.
Get rid of this crap.
Nobody wants that.
These ones are done.
Now the top.
Where...
I need my...
There.
Gimme.
That's...
Oh, I need to get up there, I think.
Hup!
That's for you.
Okay.
You can have this.
One last.
Maybe I'll give you granite.
Oh, yeah.
And we have this guy with the...
Yes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
We need digging machines!
Hello?
Oh, wait.
That comes in front.
But wait a minute.
It's gonna dig into lava first before it...
Unless we...
It's about speed.
Wait a second!
I don't have enough drills!
Uh...
Wait, no, no, no!
I do, I do, I do!
Actually, this is fine.
Because these are gonna go through...
rocks!
It's okay.
No!
Stop that.
How do I...
There we go.
No!
You cannot hit the center.
Oh, shit!
No, it's too high.
Need to go one further down.
Uh...
Oh, no...
Oh, wait, no.
Hold on.
This top one needs to be one further down.
I messed that one up.
That's on me.
Where's my deployer?
Where did you go?
Gotcha.
Here!
That's it.
Have at it.
And now this side.
It's actually better.
This is beautiful.
It's gonna work beautifully...
First try.
Let me see.
Now, it's not being dug out here.
Or up there.
Or here.
Wait.
Yeah, that's fine.
But...
These are gonna go through the walls, right?
But if we end up in a place like this, they're still gonna place it!
The problem is, obviously, we're not gonna maintain the exact shape of this 3x3 tunnel.
It's gonna be a little larger.
And maybe...
Maybe there is a way to fix that.
But...
Wait!
We can have it go behind!
We don't need to hurry!
I guess it...
Speed matters in terms of lava, but...
Honestly?
Let me...
Yeah.
Even better.
Removing it in one.
Which means...
Uh...
Oh god.
Now to figure out how the fuck to do this now.
Why won't this...
What?
Oh, did I...
Ah.
And now I need the wrench.
Hey!
First try!
Amazing.
And now since that is facing the right direction, I can just use that.
Like that.
Yeah.
It...
It doesn't need to be aligned.
Genius insight.
No!
Gimme!
Thank you.
This is so...
Cumbersome.
But it'll be worth it.
The way I did this, I aim here.
I use wrench...
There.
Nope.
Oh, so it goes opposite of where you click.
That's interesting.
Well, at least it works now.
Now we fill them up.
No.
There you go.
And...
For you.
And then we have one missing here.
What is missing?
Oh my god, I have a lot of diorite.
There you go.
Double check.
Check, check, check.
The top is also...
Guys, the top can be done better too?!
In fact...
Why do we have stone there?
Ah...
Wait.
Is there stone all the way?
There is stone all the way!
Wait, I wonder if I can...
Can I stack them like that?
I'm going a little crazy here.
But it makes sense, trust me.
Okay.
Okay, let me try...
I probably can't put it right there.
Yeah, okay.
No!
Not this again.
Okay, let me think.
So this is going to fill this wall here.
We have the bottom.
Right there.
But wait a second.
Not this one.
Wait, did I goof here?
This is going to put rails...
I...
I may have fucked this up here.
I think these needs to be one higher.
Oh, shit.
Oh, crap.
Yeah.
Yeah, this...
I messed that one up.
But I didn't though.
Block?
Not?
Yes.
That's good.
And last time I had...
Block, block...
Can't.
Wait, that should work.
Oh my god, I'm losing my mind.
Oh, man.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Honestly, let's just trust.
Trust that I got it right.
Okay.
I think it's okay.
Fuck it.
I have a good feeling about this.
Yeah, actually, it's perfect.
Yeah.
That should...
Yeah, this should work.
This should work.
I don't know what I was thinking.
This totally works.
Let's just double check everything before we start.
These have, these have, these have.
The drills are connected.
Yep.
These ones are a little high, but that's okay.
Yeah, that is the anti-lava measure.
But if we dig straight into lava, then...
Then...
Yeah, then it's not gonna work.
The front is the problem here.
Unless we place in the front before we dig.
No, that doesn't even make sense.
Let's just try it, shall we?
First things first, we gotta glue all this mess together.
Here we go.
This goes together with...
Oh, shit.
Wait, why...
Why is it yellow?
Collected blocks must be connected.
Is it not connected?
There we go.
Good.
Now we grab from inside of here.
There.
I can't grab it from here.
Here.
There.
Actually just go like that.
And then from here we go like...
There.
Oh, man.
Man, oh, man.
That looks correct.
In my opinion.
Are you ready?
I think it's time.
What happened?
Ah, but it's okay, it's okay.
I-I-I-I-I take it.
We start over?
Oh!
What?
No!
What the fuck is going on here?
Okay, it's back, it's back, it's back.
Uh, hold on.
It's fine.
It's salvaged.
Oh, no!
The blocks they were holding are gone!
What happened to them?
What the fuck is going on?
Hold on.
Um, let me get this out of here.
So, I forgot to glue this thing, obviously.
That was the problem.
Um, we need to make sure that they are not simulated anymore.
So, turn it off.
Um, we're gonna put it over here, I guess.
No, wait, how does it work?
There?
Okay.
Uh...
I guess this one can stay.
It doesn't matter?
I'm just gonna go straight through it, no?
Ah, but how do I...
Wait, maybe it's...
Yeah, actually, it's easier if I take it...
here.
And I put it...
Oh, wait, I can't.
I have to do this.
Here, and then I push it into it.
Good.
Oh, wait!
The things are back!
I guess if it's...
When it's simulated, it doesn't show them.
Oh, that's probably what it is.
Okay.
So now it's back.
Um...
And it's not simulated anymore, so we have to sort of relocate a little bit.
Give me the...
Minecart back.
Maybe I use the wrench for this.
Shit!
Fuck!
Give
me the fringe!
I mean the minecart!
What did I just destroy?
No.
Deploy, okay.
It's not that bad.
There you go, here you go.
And you were holding...
Something.
Dirt, I guess?
There you go.
Okay.
Now.
Wait.
Are we...
Oh, we're not simulated anymore.
This is a mess.
This is a real mess.
I'm not gonna lie, this is bad.
Uh, shit.
I can't even put a rail here!
This is painful.
Well, I guess I can just move it backwards into the...
Assembler.
The problem is pushing it is gonna be...
A real...
No wait, I can just do this.
Oh wait, nevermind, yeah!
The hell was I smoking?
Easy.
Okay, it is pointing the right way.
Now, are we still glued?
Kinda.
So we're missing one, obviously.
This guy, I think.
But how do I know?
I guess I could just click here and then...
Drag all the way down here.
That way it's guaranteed.
Right?
Now we should have everything glued.
Okay, I think it's time we try again.
On.
Lock rotation.
Let me just double check the last things here.
The only problem is now this bottom part is also glued.
And I think that's bad.
I don't trust...
We're gonna have to redo the gluing.
Let me do this properly.
Maybe there's an even better way of doing this.
Okay, so check it out.
We're gonna...
Go here.
Go all the way to the end like this.
That way we ensure we hit everything in between.
Right?
Now this whole line is taken care of.
Now I'm gonna go up here.
Here.
To here.
So now all of these are taken care of.
I'm gonna go up here so I can see better.
Now, next up we're gonna go from here to there.
From here to there.
Uh, I don't think these ones are...
Yeah, these ones are not part of it yet.
So we're gonna have to...
Do from here...
To there.
This one needs to be part of it too.
Same with that one.
And that should...
Do it!
I think we got it all now.
Everything has ammo.
My rail...
Guy also has ammo.
Even though I can't get to him.
This is very badly designed.
I get it, okay?
I understand.
Here we go!
Round two!
Fox three!
Faster!
Go faster!
Why won't you go faster?
Hello?
I mean, okay, lava can stream in from all sides.
Oh my god, it's horrible.
Why won't you be affected by my pushing?
Okay, there we go.
Faster!
Oh!
It's not immune to water!
Oh, crap.
The water is coming in.
Houston, we've had a problem.
Stop the water.
Where's the water come from?
Push it!
Just keep pushing.
Honestly, who cares?
Okay, so we're underwater.
Who cares?
It's not gonna stop me from realizing my dreams.
Come on.
Push, push, push, push, push.
Get some air.
Maybe this is where I need my underwater boots.
Come on, push it.
Why does that get destroyed?
Okay, so this water back here is obviously ruining things.
We gotta go plug that hole.
It has to be like a source block right up here somewhere.
Where is it?
I don't understand!
Is everything a source block?
Minecraft makes no sense.
The fuck, man?
Oh!
Nope, almost.
Yeah, this makes no sense at all.
This is ridiculous!
Give me the water!
I have no idea where you are.
I'm taking all of you.
Apparently there's water everywhere.
This makes no sense at all.
It keeps coming!
Is it the rails?
Block it!
Oh my goodness!
Did I do it?
Nope!
Jesus Christ!
Wow, I almost had an ulcer!
Okay, so obviously it's not water immune.
Or lava immune.
In fact, it's not even immune at all.
Keep going.
Why are you so slow?
Oh wait, you don't have any rails left.
Huh.
Guys, I hate this machine.
I hate it.
It's the worst thing I've ever done.
Okay, maybe...
I need to think about this.
How do we do this then?
Basically what I'm trying to do...
I'm trying to do what I'm doing here.
And also avoiding any lava and water hazards.
Because they are driving me mad.
Like they're absolutely making me go bug wild, you know?
And I can't have that.
Fill that up.
So, let me think.
Maybe I've...
Maybe I'm overthinking this actually.
So if we make a machine that...
So we know how to make a machine that just goes, right?
And makes a little rail for itself.
And a little path.
So we've done that.
Now, we need to figure out how to stop water from coming in.
Hmm...
Maybe we have a...
Oh, wait.
We have a bunch of deployers with little buckets.
Instead of one man trying to empty the...
boat...
With a bucket, we have like 12 people with buckets, you know?
Or...
We use...
Maybe there's like a create machine that sucks water in.
Like a pipe.
Ooh, actually, wait a second.
Let me think.
What kind of pipe stuff do we have?
Nah, that sounds way too fucked actually.
No, there's no way that's the solution.
So let's say I do this and it makes the path here.
And it keeps digging.
I could even have it make three.
No, just keep it simple.
One path with rails.
Good.
Let's say we open up a cave with water coming in.
What then?
Oh, I guess I could just...
A roof is all we need.
Right?
We put down a roof.
In fact, maybe we put down a roof...
It needs to be a little in front.
If we put the roof in front, it's gonna go through the rock, right?
But then it gets drilled and immediately it gets placed.
Or not...
Actually, no.
That doesn't work because it's gonna be in front.
So it never reaches that point.
But if it's behind, it's too late.
Wait.
Oh my god.
This is a real conundrum.
And I don't know how to solve it.
Maybe we just dig in places where there's no water.
You know?
Wait.
What do we know that has otherworldly hydrophobic properties?
Something that every man and child knows about.
The simplest.
The most simple construction that humans have had for thousands of years.
That's right, ladies and gentlemen.
It's the door.
The door creates holes in water pockets.
We fucking have a tunnel of doors.
Doors.
It's genius.
Like, obviously it doesn't make sense.
But in Minecraft it does, right?
It's so stupid.
Wow.
But wait a minute.
Do we need temporary doors or permanent doors?
Hmm.
Because now I'm like envisioning like a whole array of doors.
And that is very not pleasing to me.
We gotta figure out a way to somehow get rid of water.
This is like the problem.
Let's look at everything we have with pipes.
Shoots.
It's not for water, right?
That's for items.
Okay.
No.
Let's think about this.
Flywheel.
Okay.
Fluid.
Let me actually read this again.
Maybe there is a way to somehow...
I just have a feeling this won't work if it's simulated and in motion, you know?
But I could be wrong.
Yeah, that's not important.
This is not important either.
Wait!
Hold on!
I know!
I know what to do!
I got it!
I think.
When you're on a contraption that is moving, you don't need power.
You don't need gears rotating, right?
Where's my water sucker?
Is it that one?
No.
Wait.
Did I leave it outside?
Ah, there it is.
Mechanical pump is gonna pump with no gear rotation, right?
When it's on a contraption.
Let me see.
Okay, so it's not that obviously.
Maybe it even gives me a hint towards this.
There is one problem though.
Let's say I do succeed and have this suck up water.
It has to come out somewhere, right?
It doesn't just delete water.
Maybe we cannot actually delete water.
The only way is to stop water from flowing in the first place.
Okay.
No, it's not what I need.
Hmm.
Also, let's say I even have it.
Let's say I put it in the front.
It's not gonna suck up water.
What it really does is...
It sucks up water sources.
Right?
So if there's a source of water here and it flows that way...
And my guy is over here digging...
It's not gonna do anything to the water over here.
Right?
That's the problem.
I don't know how to solve this one.
I think my solution is correct.
The one I tried before.
It was just badly implemented, you know?
So obviously we had holes on the sides.
But if I can somehow make that just in time before...
Before the water comes in, then we're good, you know?
Wait a minute!
Lava maybe?
Let's say I grab lava...
Hold on, let me think.
I can neutralize lava with water, right?
Wait.
I meant we can neutralize water with lava.
Lava.
Hold on.
Wait, how does that work?
Let me actually try this.
Let me go find the lava.
I'm actually curious about this.
So let's say I have...
Water here and I grab lava.
Okay, yeah.
Then I turn my water problem into a lava problem.
That is no bueno.
We don't like that.
This is actually a horrible idea.
That's gonna make it worse.
Absolutely not.
Aw, man.
Hmm.
I could just live with it, you know?
Like, now that I have the wrench and I know how to just pick the whole thing up...
Yeah, actually, hold on.
This is the plan.
So I keep digging, right?
And as soon as shit hits the fan, I'm gonna be observant.
I'm gonna be on the lookout.
As soon as I see things go wrong, I immediately pick it up.
And take it with me.
Dude, that's actually so simple and genius.
That's all I need to do.
Hey, we solved it.
Let's go do it then.
Let's organize real quick.
We also don't need to carry around all of this stuff now.
It's a bit too much.
Put all this in here.
That way we also save this anyway.
And I can be the guy who, you know, makes the tunnel hole as we go along.
Yeah, I like that.
Because right now, all we're doing, we're making sure that we're on the right elevation and we keep digging.
It's fine.
Actually, I think we're totally killing.
What am I even doing, man?
Easy.
I overthought this one for sure.
Okay.
Time to go.
It's go time.
I still have the whole contraption with me.
Uh, actually, yeah, I do.
So maybe I should just...
real quick deploy it.
Uh, then we need to do...
this.
Just because there's all this stuff here that I can store here, right?
I also forgot to put chests on it, but, you know.
Yeah, I totally overthought this one.
Also, you know what I should have done with my theory there?
Instead of trying a 3x3, I should have just done a 1x2.
And then have it, you know, put blocks on the sides.
Actually, yeah, I'll do that.
That's a great idea.
Maybe I'll do it.
We'll see.
Maybe not.
I will take some stone, though.
I don't like the stone being in my...
in my...
inbox, I guess.
Okay!
Ready to go.
Oh, let me grab the honey.
I see that it's ready for me.
Oh, I still can't believe we aren't on the other side of the mountain yet, by the way.
Like, that just goes on forever and ever and ever.
Then again, I guess we are on the ground.
Maybe I shouldn't expect that to ever...
come out?
Hey, I don't like that, actually.
Let's dig up here.
Let's make an actual tunnel...
over in this spot.
Maybe like here.
Nah, let's go a little further.
I want to make a proper tunnel, like the Italians do, you know?
They see a mountain and they go, fuck that mountain, we don't care.
We're going through it.
That's me right now.
Nah, this... this cave is...
not... pleasing me.
I'm... dissatisfied with that cave.
Ah, man.
I kinda want this to be on the same level as my house.
Why?
Because I've got...
grand plans for the future and everything needs to connect.
Let me just...
see where I am.
Which level is my house at?
This level.
So...
we're at minus one right now.
Let's make sure that turns into a...
zero.
Zero!
Right here!
In fact, I'm just gonna dig right now.
I'm not gonna care what's in the way!
This is it!
We're digging right here!
This is actually so exciting!
Uh...
Put this here.
Lever...
I'm gonna make this in record time.
There.
Stone.
Here.
There.
Deployer.
Boop!
And we need a stone.
There.
Deployer.
Now rails.
For you.
And...
It doesn't really matter what I give you, but I'm just gonna give you diorite.
There you go.
Okay.
Now the drills.
Oh yeah!
This is actually even better.
Cause I'm gonna...
Wait, that's not a drill.
Here.
There.
Oh yeah!
Look at this!
We don't need the support structures.
We just go.
Beautiful!
Ah, this one we do need.
No, uh...
There we go.
It is ready.
Double check everything.
Make this into that.
Lock rotation.
Uh...
Yes, I think...
Oh, chest!
Chest!
Put down the chests.
Before we forget.
Hoi!
No, get up there.
Nice.
I may need to extend this a little bit, just to make it look nice.
Do we even need more than one chest?
No, we don't.
Yes, we do.
Same setup as last time.
Okay, now to glue it.
There we go.
Godspeed.
It's even gonna take out the trees.
Even though I'm producing crimes here, but...
You know, and then while it's going...
I run behind like this.
Dude, there's probably a way to automatically delete the...
You know what I mean.
Behind it.
I can't speak!
Fucking spaghetti!
It's on me.
Here, quick!
Take it!
Yes!
Wait, no.
Uh...
Oh!
Oh my god, it's working!
Holy shit!
What if it runs out mid... mid... uh... path?
Shit!
I gotta... I gotta grab these.
I'm scared of skeletons.
Please don't hit me.
Don't hurt me.
It's digging faster than I can remove these.
Wait, what?
How did that happen?
There you go.
Fresh supply.
Now we need lights.
I could even make a little light maker!
I guess.
No, we're not.
Now we're ready.
Go!
This is so sick, actually!
Woo!
Faster!
The...
Oh!
Why you stop?
Go!
Go, go, go!
Oh, it's really slow now.
Okay, it's going fast again.
Fresh supply.
There you go.
Oh, no.
You had more than me.
Now you get more from me.
This is insanely fun.
Oh, wait.
What's happening?
Oh.
I think it's slow at digging through dirt.
Like, look at that.
It's taking forever.
Oh, no, wait.
It's not dirt.
It's gotta be, um...
Gravel falling down.
That's what it is.
Yeah, that's it.
Dude, when are we coming out on the other side?
I can't wait to see that.
We're gonna have a train come through this tunnel!
But I don't know how trains work or how they even look or how big they are.
It's kind of exciting.
Do we need more rails?
Need more rails.
Wait, why did you just go backwards?
What is on the other side here?
Um...
Oh, also, I need to be careful here.
Oh, shit, this is actually about to expire.
Uh, maybe this is my cue to get out of here.
And go home with my...
ill-gotten gains.
Let's use...
this one.
Yoink!
Just picked up the whole thing.
No problem.
And I'm outta here.
In fact, I have two pickaxes now that are close to destruction.
We gotta take care of it.
Make a new pickaxe and merge it with it.
But we need iron for that.
What?
Oh my god.
This is that same frickin' place I was in.
But we should emerge on the other side at some point, right?
Because now we're actually at, uh...
non-underground level.
So this should work.
Wait, is that even gonna...
Calm down.
We're gonna have a train station here.
Oh, it...
This has...
Okay, you know what?
I'm not gonna take this down.
This looks nice.
But we're...
We're gonna put some, um...
You know how in real life there's like plants crawling up the things?
And just spreading everywhere?
I actually want that on my house as well.
You know the green ones you can put on the walls?
Maybe you can put them on the beams.
It's a slungpland.
Uh...
I don't know what it's called in English though.
Uh, let's actually quickly fix the pickaxes before I forget.
But I don't have iron.
And I need a lot.
I think.
We need blocks of iron.
And then we need anvil.
Oh, I can make it!
Sick!
Let's put it somewhere sensible.
Let's put it in the garden.
Right there!
And now...
Tell me I have diamonds.
I do indeed.
I even have sticks.
Only one though.
Which one do I save?
Probably this one.
No!
Yes, this one.
Uh, so the way this works is...
You do this...
Cost two.
Sweet.
Plus ten mining efficiency!
I don't think that's ever been in the game.
Like, where you can see that stat.
You know?
Maybe that's like...
I don't know if that's something Create is adding.
Or maybe...
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just forgetting actually.
Okay, farming.
You go in here.
Okay guys, I think we have enough cobblestone to perform...
The ritual.
Now let's revisit...
The exact procedure.
So...
Uh...
What's it called?
It's called...
Andesite.
Casing.
We need locks for that.
Got it.
Good.
Andesite alloys.
Andesite.
Which we have a lot of already, but...
It can be made...
With gravel and flint.
Which we don't care about.
But we can also make it out of diorite and cobblestone.
This is what we care about.
Which we also have a lot of.
So I'm gonna fill up my...
Oh, hold on.
Let me actually deploy this first and collect all the goods inside.
So we don't forget that we have it.
There you go.
And now with the wrench.
Boom.
Lovely.
Uh...
Maybe I shouldn't...
I mean, I could just...
I can sort of...
Have this as an ace in my pocket, right?
Instead of disassembling this, I can just keep it.
Yeah!
Actually, hold on.
I like that.
Cause now I can just go up there, grab the stuff.
Oh yeah.
Much better.
Dude, I only filled up this?!
I mean...
Not to look a gift horse in the mouth, but you know.
I'm already, you know...
Acclimating to this new reality where I can just transport infinite items.
And I'm like disappointed.
That's all I got?!
Even though what I got was way more than I usually get.
Ah!
Fuck!
I didn't do that.
Whoops.
Oh no.
Give me one.
I have done a mistake.
Put it back.
Okay.
Alright.
Uh...
Copper.
I guess we can bulk that later.
We can bulk up.
Haha.
You go there.
I think I'm gonna have to collect this again in my...
In my little...
wrench.
No.
Why didn't I fill it up?
Where's my stone too?
Did I never make one?
Let's make one.
Stone too.
Wonderful.
No.
Green.
Flint is...
melting, even though it's not.
Running out of torches here.
The lever is...
something that...
we don't need right now.
Dude, we need to create two.
We have it already.
Nice.
Now, this toolbox...
is empty.
But that's perfect, because I need it now.
I'm gonna take all the stone.
Uh...
We need diorite.
We need cobblestone.
In fact, all the...
We also need andesite, of course.
Uh...
Normal stone, we actually do not need.
I guess we could use gravel.
But then again, we don't have flint.
Doesn't matter then.
Damn, I have a lot of andesite.
Sweet.
Then we have diorite, cobblestone.
Damn.
We need more diorite, actually.
So I guess that's the first part of the whole machinery.
Now we have to decide where the factory is gonna be.
Also, let me pick this up before I forget.
Ah, but hold on a minute.
This one is wrong.
Wait, how do I pick this up?
Do I have to connect it again first?
I may have to.
We also have too much cobblestone.
Hey, Jackie.
Oh, I know it's eating time.
I'll be there in a sec.
Think, think.
This one.
Man, where did I just put the frickin' thing?
Oh.
Here.
Uh, then we also need the lever, of course.
Which I just put away.
Classic.
No, actually, I don't need the lever because it needs to be off.
Uh...
Wait a second.
Something's off here.
This, this, uh, no.
Um...
It needs to be on.
Yeah.
Now we put in, uh...
Minecart.
And...
There we go.
So now...
This...
Right click.
Ah, shit!
Huh?
Why is it not...
Connected?
Oh!
Wait, no.
I don't understand.
That, that makes no sense.
I need glue.
Is it not all connected here?
Okay, now...
That is...
Why is this connected down there?
Dude, it's all...
It is all connected.
Let me redo it.
Maybe it's bugged.
Who knows what's happening.
Ah, we broke it.
There.
And now this is a machine I will always carry around in my pocket.
Using the wrench.
There we go.
And there it is.
It is now in my pocket.
Very cool.
Now we fill this up with all the stone that we have.
Not this.
I think that was it.
No diorite left.
Oh, we also have this up here.
Look at all that.
Where are all my rails?
Are they...
Maybe they're still on the deployer, actually.
Okay, then we need belts.
We have deployers.
Uh...
I think.
Did I leave them here?
Deployer.
There they are.
And I think I'm also gonna need a bunch of...
I'm gonna need depots.
I'm gonna need mixing basins and all kinds of crap here.
There's actually a lot we need.
How expensive is that to make?
Mixing.
Mix...
Mechanical mixer.
Needs whisks.
These are easy.
What about a whisk?
And this side...
Oh man, I need iron.
I am lacking iron right now.
Let's go make some iron pressed.
Or sheets.
With the press.
Okay.
Uh...
But I guess I can take some of this and these.
Oh, these one needs to be pressed as well.
We can cook that.
Yep.
What about the depot?
Oh, that's super easy.
Okay, we need casings.
Which means wood.
And alloys.
Which we also need more of.
But we...
Oh man.
We need a lot of andesite.
So we can make a lot of andesite.
There's also nuggets we can turn into bars.
Or ingots.
Good.
I'm gonna get my checklist real quick actually.
Because I think we need this.
Okay.
Fuck this.
We don't need this anymore.
Operation.
Make factory.
No.
Make assembly.
For andesite casing.
What we need...
Let's just go through the process here.
One more.
Once more here.
So we need...
Deployer with andesite alloy.
So...
One deployer.
One...
Depot.
We have that.
Uh...
Yeah.
Deploy andesite alloy on...
Stripped wood.
Uh...
Strip wood with deployer.
And axe.
Mix.
Right?
And...
Let me see.
Then we have to mix.
Or...
What was it?
Yeah.
Andesite with zinc or iron nuggets.
Mix andesite and zinc.
Uh...
Slash...
Iron...
Nuggets.
For...
Uh...
I forgot what I was making just now.
What did I just say?
Oh, for the end...
For the alloy, of course.
Okay.
And we're gonna...
Basically, we're gonna need a lot of basins.
Uh...
Before I write that...
Let me just double check here.
Now that we make that...
And we have this.
Andesite is, of course, being made by...
Uh...
Gravel.
But that's not what we want.
We want this.
Diorite and cobblestone.
Right?
And the automated shapeless crafting.
So, it's basically just the mixer again.
Yeah.
Andesite made from mixing...
Cobblestone and diorite.
We need...
Mixer...
I'm just gonna say at least five of each just to have.
Also for the future.
More than five mixers.
Basins.
Depots.
Deployers.
Uh...
And of course, belts are...
You know...
An obvious thing.
We need...
Belts.
Let's just say...
Over a hundred belts.
Uh...
We need, um...
Rods.
Whatever they were called.
The spinny ones.
Spinny rods.
And...
Power swords, of course.
To power all of it.
That's it.
Yep.
Do...
Not...
Get distracted.
You will do this...
Now.
And that's for me in the future.
I'm even gonna hold the thing right here...
In my hands.
So that when I come back...
I will look at it.
And I will not forget that we're doing this.
I will not be distracted by anything.
We're making that happen next time.
What do you say to that?
I think the first automation...
Factory style is coming in soon.
We have everything we need.
GG.
Yeah, thank you.
Nice job, team.
Too much rage bait.
Was there rage bait today?
It's unintentional, guys, if there's any.
I'm not intentionally rage baiting.
In fact, from now on, I will hold up my hand every time I intentionally rage bait.
So you know when I'm doing it.
Cogs are back.
Hell yeah.
Dude, it feels so good to stream again.
I missed this.
Rage bait is always present.
It's inevitable.
I mean, it is.
This is a very complex mod, you know?
And...
It's inevitable that I am missing something very obvious and very efficient.
But that's the path, you know?
You start with the inefficient system and then you build on top of it and you learn better ways to do it.
And I think that's really fun.
Yeah, it is a very complex mod.
That's why I'm so happy that, you know, it's being fed to me slowly.
And not just everything at once.
Please do a blind playthrough with girlfriend?
Oh, you mean like me going out in public, live streaming it and being like, Guys, don't give me any tips.
I'm gonna pick up this girl on my own, okay?
I will... I will fail.
There will be some rage bait.
There will be some masturbate.
Just kidding.
But, uh, I know what you meant.
I don't have a girlfriend though.
Just messing with you guys.
Let me turn that down just a bit.
In public?!
Nah.
Cranking his cog, live.
No, stop.
You guys, you need to come up with better jokes.
That one's old.
Just don't treat her like Claire?
Honestly, I could only wish for a girlfriend like Claire.
She was the best there is.
She died trying to protect my TV.
I mean, if that isn't undying love and...
Loyalty, then I don't know what is.
Who's Claire?
Claire is a character from The Sims.
She died in a fire.
Nah, I'm not gonna... I'm not gonna reveal too much.
In case you ever want to watch that, because it's kind of funny.
Let's just say Claire will be missed.
Exactly, I do have a TV now.
Oliver, are those checklists from CreateMod?
Which checklist do you mean?
You mean the one I made at the end?
If that's what you mean, then yes.
Those clipboards are from Create.
And they're awesome.
How's the new place?
It's amazing.
I think it's like 40% bigger.
If you just calculate it, you know, from square meters.
Compared to my last place.
So there's room now for a proper couch and a TV.
And there's way more room for Jackie to run around in too, which is awesome.
So when we play, you know, she can have much more freedom.
It's super nice.
I still haven't put up her stuff on the walls yet.
Because the walls are made of concrete and it's a pain in the ass to drill into.
I need hammer drills and...
Yeah, I can only drill at certain times because, you know, it's making a lot of noise.
And it's also so annoying to do.
I'm also bad at it, you know.
Did you buy it?
No, no, no.
I'm renting it.
Did I buy it?
This would cost millions to buy.
I'm not even kidding.
Probably like 5 million kroners if you were to buy an apartment like this.
Which is like a million dollars.
I don't need to...
It's fine, guys.
I'm fine.
I don't mind renting.
I actually like it.
It means I don't have to care about taking care of the place, you know?
The landlord takes care of that.
In a way, it's kind of freeing.
But obviously, you know, you pay every month and that's kind of bad too.
Do you know what the next stream is?
Probably tomorrow.
Because right now I'm still deciding what to play off stream as well.
And I haven't even started that yet.
So for now, I'm probably just gonna stream a bunch.
Stream a bunch.
Like, normally I would do at least a daybreak between, but since I don't play anything off stream right now.
Or when I say off stream, I mean like local recording.
You know, the one I put on YouTube that I don't stream.
Yeah, I would say tomorrow stream.
Does this apartment have AC?
No, it doesn't.
But it does because I bought an AC at my old place that I then brought over here.
The problem now is, ironically, it's not actually helping me much.
Because I can't put the AC in my room that I'm playing in that I could in the old place because I'm on the second floor now.
And there's no way to put the outside unit outside my window.
It's a long story.
So the only way for me to have the outside unit is to put it on the little balcony I have, which is in the living room.
And since this place is bigger, the cooling is not enough to actually reach my room.
You know, there's not enough air mixing going around.
So I actually looked into getting a fiber optic DisplayPort cable and USB cables.
And then finally, once and for all, just move the damn computer outside the gaming room.
Have it in a whole different room where it can heat up that room instead, you know?
And that way Jackie gets heated up as well at the same time.
It's genius.
And that way I also don't have to listen to the computer fans and you know when he goes brrr Get my computer off somewhere else.
It's something I've been thinking about for a while, and it just, you know...
Dang, how rich are you?
I'm not rich.
At all.
But I need to do this, you know?
Otherwise I die of heat during the summer.
But dude, those fiber optic cables are so expensive, it's crazy.
Are you aware of the telepathy people do here?
I am aware of it.
It's like an inside joke, right?
Of some sort.
It works?
It's real.
Are you sure you don't just have confirmation bias?
PC in other room catches fire whilst playing is a bad idea?
I mean...
Why would it catch fire?
That doesn't make sense.
I mean, you are right that if it were to catch fire that I wouldn't notice it as fast.
I think if it caught fire, I would notice it at some point anyway, because it probably would affect my game.
That I'm playing.
How do you think you get ideas?
Oh my god, you're right.
That's the explanation.
It's you guys planting ideas in my head subconsciously.
Via small tubes inserted in my brain.
I don't think a PC does randomly catch fire.
Unless... Actually, I have heard this before.
That on some GPUs, if the power cable isn't connected properly, it can actually burn out.
I don't know if it can start a fire, though.
I mean, I guess it would have to be pretty extreme, but...
It could happen, I guess?
It's not impossible.
Oh, by the way, I forgot to mention this at the start of the stream.
I also put it as a rule on Twitch now, but from now on, we're only gonna have English in the chat.
If you don't mind.
Because it's just a mess to keep track of with different languages.
And it's just easier for people to read.
So we're just gonna go full English.
Apparently, the Tower of Babel was erected one of these streams.
Which is not good.
I mean, it was kind of funny, I guess.
That you did that, but, you know.
We gotta keep it English.
Even Danish is...
You know, it's gonna be a very big minority, so I would say only English.
I am the only one who is allowed to speak different languages.
And I will speak different languages at times.
Because I think it's fun.
But that's me, I get privileges, you know.
I can speak other languages, you can't.
A tyrant rules the stream.
That's right, and don't you forget it.
The reason is that it bypasses auto-mod.
I'm not sure if that's true.
How would German streams manage their chat then?
You know?
Unless it's based on what the stream language is set to.
Maybe that's a thing, actually.
Yeah, don't test it.
If you speak other languages, I will ban you personally.
And you will never be allowed to be here again.
The tyrant has spoken.
The banhammer will come in.
Now, I'll probably give you a warning first.
But then the banhammer will come in.
And it's gonna be a hard one.
This one feels personal.
I'm just messing with you.
It's not that personal.
It's just also harder to keep track of when there's different languages, you know.
I don't know what you're saying.
If you're speaking a language, I don't understand.
And you could be saying things that break TOS, right?
Which is not good.
Also, it's not as fun if I can't read what you're writing right now.
If you were to speak Spanish, I can't really communicate with you.
Which type of English?
Old English only.
Think 1920s English.
You may not speak modern English.
What if I say Sul Sul?
You can say Sul Sul.
That's okay.
Everyone, learn ye olde English.
Right, I'm thinking of...
Maybe we should pull it even further back.
Back to...
What's that guy called?
The guy who's like really English and he is...
Like pretty good at writing things apparently, like plays.
Oh yeah, Shakespeare.
That's the guy, right?
Shakespeare style only.
I think that could actually be kind of funny.
I wish I could speak Shakespearean style.
Because I think it sounds really hilarious.
There's this line that I really like.
I forgot how it goes, but it's something along the lines of...
Oh, how I wish...
I was the glove...
On thy hand so that I might touch thy skin or something, you know?
I always thought that was really cool.
I butchered that quote, but you know what I mean.
I wish I were a bird.
Is that a line?
He just wrote, I wish I were a bird.
Can I speak Iridian?
What is that?
Is that a real language?
Sorry if it is.
I don't know about Iridia if that's a place.
Oh, she doth teach the torches to burn bright.
Exactly, that's good.
Oliver, were you a flight sim guy at some point?
I still am.
I love flight sims.
I play Microsoft Flight Simulator 2024.
Now and then.
Off stream though.
Yeah.
I'm not very good at it though.
I used to know some stuff about aviation.
You know, watching YouTube tutorials and just learning about aviation in general.
It was fun.
You fly on VATSIM.
I did a couple times.
You can watch my videos on YouTube.
I have some videos on it.
I have like three or four videos about VATSIM on my channel.
You can check it out.
Be warned though, it's very bad, okay?
I'm very amateurish.
And it's like my first times in VATSIM.
You know, it's like a learning thing.
People told me they learned a lot from it though.
Because I make a lot of mistakes in those videos.
And you know, I put it out there.
People couldn't see it.
Yeah, I just...
We're about to end right now, OneHumor.
It came in...
Right at the wrong time, I guess.
Iridium is from Project Hail Mary.
A book which you need to listen to the audiobook of...
It might be the perfect audiobook ever for you specifically.
Okay.
I mean, if it's better than the movie, then I'm down for it.
If it's worse than the movie, then I don't know if I want it, right?
I mean, the movie was fine.
It just didn't blow me away, I guess.
I have seen Blade Runner, I love it.
The first time I saw Blade Runner 2, I didn't actually like it that much.
But I've seen it a couple times since, and now I think it's growing on me.
I think I like it quite a bit now.
The first one is still goaded for me though.
I just love the ambiance and the music and the...
This feeling you get when you watch it, you know?
Like there's this scene where...
Spoiler alert if you haven't seen the movie, I'm just gonna say it anyway, right?
Where there's this woman running and she has this transparent sort of raincoat on.
And it's in slow motion and this music is playing while she's falling through the glass.
Dude, it is honestly like...
Such a masterpiece.
Those scenes exist in so many places in that movie.
Where just the visuals and the music make you feel a certain kind of way, you know?
Like I wanna cry during those scenes, but I don't know why.
It's not joy or sadness, it's like a weird...
State of being.
That just produces tears for me.
You know what I mean by that?
It's just so good.
Have you thought of playing Project Somboid?
I have actually.
The first thing I thought when I saw screenshots of it...
Is that it looks like The Sims.
Specifically The Sims 1.
I mean, try and compare screenshots between The Sims 1 and Project Somboid.
It has to be inspired by The Sims.
At least from the art style.
The Sims gone wrong, exactly!
Maybe add it as a mod to The Sims, you know?
You're just out there, you know, going to work, coming home, taking a poop, washing yourself in the shower, making food, and then all of a sudden...
Zombie Apocalypse.
And we're now on Project Somboid.
I think that could be a fun mod.
I heard it's very difficult though.
Like, it's very difficult.
And very punishing.
Hey Jackie!
I know, I'm coming now.
Alright guys, I'm going.
Thank you so much for showing up to this.
This was great, it's good to be back.
Stream tomorrow.
99% chance of stream tomorrow.
And I'll see you around, it's time to feed myself and Jackie.
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.